[
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 6771.935000000667,
		"rt_considerations" : 27646.47999999943,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "potato",
		"consideration2" : "carrots",
		"consideration3" : "pepper",
		"consideration4" : "cucumber",
		"consideration5" : "corn",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 5816.604999999981,
		"rt_considerations" : 14218.455000000176,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "underwear",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "tanktop",
		"consideration5" : "coat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 5337.330000000293,
		"rt_considerations" : 13082.909999999174,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "lion",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 4390.8250000004045,
		"rt_considerations" : 19086.019999998825,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "toaster oven",
		"consideration3" : "air fryer",
		"consideration4" : "processor",
		"consideration5" : "toaster",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 6047.650000000431,
		"rt_considerations" : 12423.704999999245,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "4th of july",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "halloween",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 5553.3550000000105,
		"rt_considerations" : 20772.559999999445,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "golden carrol",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "ceral",
		"rt_response" : 6687.595000001253,
		"rt_considerations" : 16029.334999999264,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "banana",
		"consideration3" : "yogurt",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 4477.305000000342,
		"rt_considerations" : 11175.145000001066,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "softball",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "football",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 25079.49000000005,
		"rt_considerations" : 8097.6350000000675,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AG491SO5WFQ8X",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teacher",
		"rt_response" : 6075.005000000587,
		"rt_considerations" : 13962.395000000484,
		"age" : 23,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "sv9bot6xulq8",
		"consideration1" : "construction ",
		"consideration2" : "retail",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Jacket",
		"rt_response" : 11293.77500002738,
		"rt_considerations" : 28203.84999999078,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "Socks",
		"consideration2" : "Sweaters",
		"consideration3" : "Hoodies",
		"consideration4" : "t-shirts",
		"consideration5" : "scarves",
		"consideration6" : "hats",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Soccer",
		"rt_response" : 10018.530000001192,
		"rt_considerations" : 16672.27499996079,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "skateboarding",
		"consideration5" : "skating",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "folding table",
		"rt_response" : 13176.285000052303,
		"rt_considerations" : 15015.445000026375,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "ottoman",
		"consideration4" : "end table",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Presidents Day",
		"rt_response" : 15412.300000025425,
		"rt_considerations" : 27953.84999999078,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "Columbus Day",
		"consideration2" : "Halloween",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 15088.850000000093,
		"rt_considerations" : 14583.440000016708,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "blender",
		"consideration4" : "food processor",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Parfait",
		"rt_response" : 8465.275000024121,
		"rt_considerations" : 10537.494999996852,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "bacon",
		"consideration4" : "sausage",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Prostitution",
		"rt_response" : 6354.229999997187,
		"rt_considerations" : 18202.244999993127,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "farming",
		"consideration2" : "homemaking",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 6252.635000040755,
		"rt_considerations" : 11508.769999956712,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "Tiger",
		"consideration2" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration3" : "Monkey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomatoes",
		"rt_response" : 15783.785000036005,
		"rt_considerations" : 13286.890000046697,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "cabbage",
		"consideration2" : "lettuce",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3GAQNTZ1V1VO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Chima Brazilian Steaks",
		"rt_response" : 13199.23500000732,
		"rt_considerations" : 7585.409999999683,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "United States of America",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "uzee1ashl5yu",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 7683.1400000082795,
		"rt_considerations" : 51485.50999999861,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "X Mas",
		"consideration2" : "Saint Nicks Day",
		"consideration3" : "Christmas",
		"consideration4" : "Holiday",
		"consideration5" : "Jesus Birthday",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 7837.96999999322,
		"rt_considerations" : 20677.9899999965,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "bacon",
		"consideration2" : "sausage",
		"consideration3" : "pancakes",
		"consideration4" : "cereal",
		"consideration5" : "waffles",
		"consideration6" : "toast",
		"consideration7" : "bagels",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 5334.18000000529,
		"rt_considerations" : 17478.020000009565,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "audoman",
		"consideration3" : "folding chair",
		"consideration4" : "stool",
		"consideration5" : "table",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 3477.98499999044,
		"rt_considerations" : 18069.945000010193,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "lacrosse",
		"consideration6" : "handball",
		"consideration7" : "tennis",
		"consideration8" : "swimming"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 6326.195000001462,
		"rt_considerations" : 21269.954999996116,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "Hardees",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "Five Guys",
		"consideration5" : "Pancheros",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Hat",
		"rt_response" : 5245.974999997998,
		"rt_considerations" : 17324.045000001206,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "Shirt",
		"consideration2" : "Pants",
		"consideration3" : "Shoes",
		"consideration4" : "Belt",
		"consideration5" : "Tie",
		"consideration6" : "Coat",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "fisherman",
		"rt_response" : 10806.039999995846,
		"rt_considerations" : 17717.994999999064,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "farmer",
		"consideration2" : "carpenter",
		"consideration3" : "gladiator",
		"consideration4" : "priest",
		"consideration5" : "singer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Tomato",
		"rt_response" : 5662.100000001374,
		"rt_considerations" : 29909.854999990785,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "Apples",
		"consideration2" : "Peppers",
		"consideration3" : "Carrots",
		"consideration4" : "Corn",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Fish",
		"rt_response" : 4830.2850000036415,
		"rt_considerations" : 17469.75499999826,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Panda",
		"consideration4" : "Bear",
		"consideration5" : "Bird",
		"consideration6" : "Snake",
		"consideration7" : "Cheetah",
		"consideration8" : "Leopard"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AFRKVRPZ2RHY8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Toaster",
		"rt_response" : 4174.050000001444,
		"rt_considerations" : 26699.56500000262,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "gk61wdssztbu",
		"consideration1" : "Stove",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Breadmaker",
		"consideration4" : "Coffeemaker",
		"consideration5" : "Can Opener",
		"consideration6" : "Spoon",
		"consideration7" : "Mixer",
		"consideration8" : "Blender"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 4628.049999999348,
		"rt_considerations" : 33643.364999996265,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pepper",
		"rt_response" : 38019.67999999761,
		"rt_considerations" : 33491.01500000688,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration2" : "cucumber",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 5018.199999991339,
		"rt_considerations" : 28549.514999991516,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "wendys",
		"consideration2" : "red lobster",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "military",
		"rt_response" : 9521.585000009509,
		"rt_considerations" : 17543.04499999853,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "teaching",
		"consideration2" : "dmv",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 3801.0750000103144,
		"rt_considerations" : 15154.054999991786,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 4124.085000003106,
		"rt_considerations" : 25147.335000001476,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "coffee table",
		"consideration2" : "lamp",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "hippopotamus",
		"rt_response" : 9596.760000000359,
		"rt_considerations" : 21646.655000004102,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "zebra",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "bear",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 5131.059999999707,
		"rt_considerations" : 22257.94000001042,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "easter",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 4835.520000007818,
		"rt_considerations" : 17002.189999999246,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "jackets",
		"consideration2" : "coats",
		"consideration3" : "sweaters",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "shirts",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1ZLHNJEURLK3O",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 7707.880000001751,
		"rt_considerations" : 16350.680000003194,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "17y93hrpur1c",
		"consideration1" : "spatula",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Doctor",
		"rt_response" : 13655.644999991637,
		"rt_considerations" : 34645.635000022594,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Doctor",
		"consideration2" : "Neurologist",
		"consideration3" : "Driver",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Suit",
		"rt_response" : 8344.029999978375,
		"rt_considerations" : 14364.444999955595,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Suit",
		"consideration2" : "Coat",
		"consideration3" : "Dress",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Halloween",
		"rt_response" : 6514.980000036303,
		"rt_considerations" : 21210.01999999862,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Christmas",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Microwave",
		"rt_response" : 15353.07000001194,
		"rt_considerations" : 12429.264999984298,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Microwave",
		"consideration2" : "Refrigerator",
		"consideration3" : "Dishwasher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 4533.915000036359,
		"rt_considerations" : 11253.354999993462,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Basketball",
		"consideration3" : "Fencing",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 9141.115000005811,
		"rt_considerations" : 10626.950000005309,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Tomato",
		"rt_response" : 25343.97500002524,
		"rt_considerations" : 13189.580000005662,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Tomato",
		"consideration2" : "Broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "Carrot",
		"consideration4" : "Green peas",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Bacon",
		"rt_response" : 4141.829999978654,
		"rt_considerations" : 7829.165000002831,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Bacon",
		"consideration2" : "Eggs",
		"consideration3" : "Bread",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 8917.755000002217,
		"rt_considerations" : 9829.335000016727,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Couch",
		"consideration2" : "Mattress",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A122LRCSBAD6DC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Chimpanzee",
		"rt_response" : 9309.780000010505,
		"rt_considerations" : 14117.114999971818,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "u51832bl85a4",
		"consideration1" : "Chimpanzee",
		"consideration2" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "Lion",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 9139.415000041481,
		"rt_considerations" : 44024.29500001017,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "refridgerator",
		"consideration4" : "toaster oven",
		"consideration5" : "oven",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "breakfast sandwich",
		"rt_response" : 15825.939999951515,
		"rt_considerations" : 27328.395000018645,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "bagel",
		"consideration4" : "banana",
		"consideration5" : "english muffin",
		"consideration6" : "bacon",
		"consideration7" : "ham",
		"consideration8" : "breakfast sandwich"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 11577.019999967888,
		"rt_considerations" : 37327.62499997625,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "stool",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "clock",
		"consideration4" : "bat",
		"consideration5" : "trash can",
		"consideration6" : "chair",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "biologist",
		"rt_response" : 23524.014999973588,
		"rt_considerations" : 37665.94499995699,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "air traffic controller",
		"consideration2" : "teacher",
		"consideration3" : "scientist",
		"consideration4" : "biologist",
		"consideration5" : "researcher",
		"consideration6" : "doctor",
		"consideration7" : "eye doctor",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "taco bell",
		"rt_response" : 42436.74000003375,
		"rt_considerations" : 24390.465000004042,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "taco bell",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "wendys",
		"consideration4" : "starbucks",
		"consideration5" : "outback",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 14256.67999999132,
		"rt_considerations" : 18915.79499997897,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "cow",
		"consideration2" : "ant",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "lion",
		"consideration5" : "gazelle",
		"consideration6" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration7" : "fish",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "brussel sprouts",
		"rt_response" : 7888.6400000192225,
		"rt_considerations" : 17278.7000000244,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "broccoli",
		"consideration2" : "brussel sprouts",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 4870.554999972228,
		"rt_considerations" : 19382.67999998061,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "basketball",
		"consideration6" : "lacrossee",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "arbor day",
		"rt_response" : 5570.805000024848,
		"rt_considerations" : 21805.30499998713,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "labor day",
		"consideration2" : "flag day",
		"consideration3" : "arbor day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AOJPRTHGMEPFX",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "hats",
		"rt_response" : 6760.264999989886,
		"rt_considerations" : 18732.970000011846,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "36cbm16ruzk2",
		"consideration1" : "hat",
		"consideration2" : "socks",
		"consideration3" : "belt",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "shorts",
		"consideration6" : "shoes",
		"consideration7" : "t shirt",
		"consideration8" : "beanie"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Fold up chair",
		"rt_response" : 12555.410000029951,
		"rt_considerations" : 46465.754999779165,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Fold up chair",
		"consideration2" : "Desk",
		"consideration3" : "Couch",
		"consideration4" : "Bookshelf",
		"consideration5" : "Ottoman",
		"consideration6" : "Coffee table",
		"consideration7" : "TV stand",
		"consideration8" : "Dinner tray"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 18432.634999975562,
		"rt_considerations" : 24152.730000205338,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Cereal",
		"consideration2" : "Bagels",
		"consideration3" : "Donut",
		"consideration4" : "Eggs",
		"consideration5" : "Oatmeal",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years",
		"rt_response" : 10233.16999990493,
		"rt_considerations" : 31959.90000013262,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "New Years",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Easter",
		"consideration5" : "Independence Day",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 7924.885000102222,
		"rt_considerations" : 27607.53499995917,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Soccer",
		"consideration3" : "Disc Golf",
		"consideration4" : "Hockey",
		"consideration5" : "Baseball",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "QSR Clerk",
		"rt_response" : 10950.205000117421,
		"rt_considerations" : 34588.41500012204,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "QSR Clerk",
		"consideration2" : "Janitor",
		"consideration3" : "Teacher",
		"consideration4" : "Bus driver",
		"consideration5" : "Accountant",
		"consideration6" : "Ride Share Driver",
		"consideration7" : "Forklift Driver",
		"consideration8" : "Grocery clerk"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Avocado",
		"rt_response" : 9459.430000279099,
		"rt_considerations" : 18395.999999716878,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Avocado",
		"consideration2" : "Orange",
		"consideration3" : "Apple",
		"consideration4" : "Peaches",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 8041.629999876022,
		"rt_considerations" : 23620.839999988675,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Opossum",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Blender",
		"rt_response" : 3857.074999716133,
		"rt_considerations" : 24988.49999997765,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Blender",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Tea maker",
		"consideration4" : "Stove",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Jacket",
		"rt_response" : 10650.65999981016,
		"rt_considerations" : 17998.43499995768,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Jacket",
		"consideration2" : "Blouse",
		"consideration3" : "Hat",
		"consideration4" : "Shirt",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23ONWDSVICDCY",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Popeyes",
		"rt_response" : 9126.605000346899,
		"rt_considerations" : 35870.349999982864,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "U.S.A.",
		"nationality" : "American ",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "oztleqgnnbr7",
		"consideration1" : "Popeyes",
		"consideration2" : "MacDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Arbys",
		"consideration4" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration5" : "Wendys",
		"consideration6" : "Chik Fil A",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Track",
		"rt_response" : 8143.965000053868,
		"rt_considerations" : 37969.34999991208,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "wrestling",
		"consideration5" : "tennis",
		"consideration6" : "track",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 8256.59500004258,
		"rt_considerations" : 18826.93000009749,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "peppers",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 8559.68499998562,
		"rt_considerations" : 20586.74499997869,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "waffles",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "pancakes",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Blender",
		"rt_response" : 7159.100000048056,
		"rt_considerations" : 19079.335000016727,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "blender",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "tie",
		"rt_response" : 5057.039999985136,
		"rt_considerations" : 16215.369999990799,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "belt",
		"consideration3" : "tie",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Taco Bell",
		"rt_response" : 26021.65500004776,
		"rt_considerations" : 20497.229999979027,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "wendys",
		"consideration4" : "checkers",
		"consideration5" : "taco bell",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "sales",
		"rt_response" : 7343.405000050552,
		"rt_considerations" : 22384.330000029877,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "manager",
		"consideration2" : "warehouse",
		"consideration3" : "sales",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 11018.14500009641,
		"rt_considerations" : 38616.225000005215,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "bear",
		"consideration5" : "giraffe",
		"consideration6" : "monkey",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of july",
		"rt_response" : 10167.365000001155,
		"rt_considerations" : 15995.75499992352,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "halloween",
		"consideration3" : "4th of july",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1GZCLBFBKWFEZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "stool",
		"rt_response" : 10366.16000009235,
		"rt_considerations" : 20714.384999941103,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "4sr6x2k7fqso",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "ottoman",
		"consideration4" : "stool",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "basketball",
		"rt_response" : 7532.354999999807,
		"rt_considerations" : 25238.46499999991,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "gymnastics",
		"consideration5" : "golf",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 5535.79499999978,
		"rt_considerations" : 23469.105000000127,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "carrots",
		"consideration2" : "broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 3638.1099999998696,
		"rt_considerations" : 17837.010000000184,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "coffee grinder",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 6312.66999999978,
		"rt_considerations" : 16233.990000000194,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "bacon",
		"consideration4" : "pancakes",
		"consideration5" : "waffles",
		"consideration6" : "french toast",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 4117.109999999695,
		"rt_considerations" : 18655.455000000075,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "monkey",
		"consideration4" : "penguin",
		"consideration5" : "gorilla",
		"consideration6" : "lion",
		"consideration7" : "tiger",
		"consideration8" : "cheetah"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "pants",
		"rt_response" : 6570.125000000175,
		"rt_considerations" : 15943.320000000298,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "shoes",
		"consideration3" : "shirts",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "counselor",
		"rt_response" : 4390.6650000003865,
		"rt_considerations" : 21620.110000000277,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "police officer",
		"consideration2" : "dispatcher",
		"consideration3" : "call service rep",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 9491.054999999935,
		"rt_considerations" : 12007.559999999998,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "Chilis",
		"consideration2" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "table",
		"rt_response" : 12032.869999999995,
		"rt_considerations" : 13954.255000000063,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "sofa",
		"consideration3" : "chair",
		"consideration4" : "desk",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ER0EVZ7E1Z8G",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 10518.150000000373,
		"rt_considerations" : 15514.20000000007,
		"age" : 44,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "r7x4hfqp69jl",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Kwanzaa",
		"consideration4" : "Easter",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "cheesecake factory",
		"rt_response" : 12211.799999990035,
		"rt_considerations" : 46512.30499998201,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "chicken parm",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "french toast",
		"consideration4" : "pizza",
		"consideration5" : "hamburgers",
		"consideration6" : "chicken sandwiches",
		"consideration7" : "sliders",
		"consideration8" : "egg rolls"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years",
		"rt_response" : 6477.890000038315,
		"rt_considerations" : 30726.57999995863,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "coffee maker",
		"rt_response" : 8140.484999981709,
		"rt_considerations" : 32003.750000032596,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "wolf",
		"rt_response" : 13530.449999962002,
		"rt_considerations" : 18981.170000042766,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "bear",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 5396.869999996852,
		"rt_considerations" : 17032.719999959227,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "sausage",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 11062.660000054166,
		"rt_considerations" : 21236.56500002835,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "table",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "prostitution",
		"rt_response" : 7162.865000020247,
		"rt_considerations" : 16527.479999989737,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "basketball",
		"rt_response" : 6492.224999994505,
		"rt_considerations" : 14596.149999997579,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "foorball",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jacket",
		"rt_response" : 6467.690000019502,
		"rt_considerations" : 13188.175000017509,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "skirt",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A27PVIL93ZMY46",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "jicama",
		"rt_response" : 6380.074999993667,
		"rt_considerations" : 16883.0200000084,
		"age" : 41,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "tmd5jw7rkz3v",
		"consideration1" : "potato",
		"consideration2" : "carrot",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "can opener",
		"rt_response" : 12531.380000000354,
		"rt_considerations" : 37247.575000001234,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "firdge",
		"consideration2" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration3" : "oven",
		"consideration4" : "stove",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "pelican",
		"rt_response" : 15399.265000000014,
		"rt_considerations" : 23447.449999999662,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "duck",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "truck driver",
		"rt_response" : 8797.664999998233,
		"rt_considerations" : 14177.52499999915,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "waitress",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 23938.73000000167,
		"rt_considerations" : 30489.55500000011,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "lamp",
		"consideration2" : "shelf",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 6748.184999996738,
		"rt_considerations" : 12528.570000002219,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 6521.720000004279,
		"rt_considerations" : 11627.309999996214,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "wrestling",
		"rt_response" : 14858.230000005278,
		"rt_considerations" : 12389.42500000121,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "lacrosse",
		"consideration2" : "golf",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "independence day",
		"rt_response" : 15919.795000001614,
		"rt_considerations" : 18742.435000000114,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "easter",
		"consideration2" : "flag day",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "baconsausage",
		"rt_response" : 20558.514999996987,
		"rt_considerations" : 16181.144999995013,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "coffee",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "banana"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EH7IQCDH2Q5D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "applebees",
		"rt_response" : 8077.360000002955,
		"rt_considerations" : 9144.640000005893,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "zdqy6wg5h1z0",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St. Patricks day",
		"rt_response" : 9295.020000001387,
		"rt_considerations" : 26755.385000000388,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Valentines day",
		"consideration2" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration3" : "Memorial Day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Sofa",
		"rt_response" : 6601.479999997537,
		"rt_considerations" : 17941.695000001346,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Chairs",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Prostitute",
		"rt_response" : 9660.149999999703,
		"rt_considerations" : 21057.7200000007,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Butcher",
		"consideration2" : "Baker",
		"consideration3" : "Horseshoe maker",
		"consideration4" : "Smithing",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Tennis",
		"rt_response" : 11981.830000000627,
		"rt_considerations" : 17979.459999998653,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "polo",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "football",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 8781.600000002072,
		"rt_considerations" : 30277.649999999994,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "TGI Fridays",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Blender",
		"rt_response" : 3725.799999996525,
		"rt_considerations" : 9417.819999998756,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Pants",
		"rt_response" : 4045.685000000958,
		"rt_considerations" : 9123.87999999919,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Shirt",
		"consideration2" : "Shoes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Potato",
		"rt_response" : 5683.774999997695,
		"rt_considerations" : 21151.55500000037,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "eggplant",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Penguin ",
		"rt_response" : 8598.480000000563,
		"rt_considerations" : 10867.72000000201,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Elephant",
		"consideration4" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2UIGDOLX5RV95",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Donuts",
		"rt_response" : 22244.59999999823,
		"rt_considerations" : 10695.840000000317,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "c3ee7e2wtjoc",
		"consideration1" : "Cereal and milk",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Shark",
		"rt_response" : 10665,
		"rt_considerations" : 25250,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Whale",
		"consideration2" : "Dolphin",
		"consideration3" : "Lizard",
		"consideration4" : "Shark",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Soccer",
		"rt_response" : 21598,
		"rt_considerations" : 15485,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Basketball",
		"consideration4" : "Soccer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 13176,
		"rt_considerations" : 18599,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Sausage",
		"consideration2" : "Eggs",
		"consideration3" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Call center representative",
		"rt_response" : 46995,
		"rt_considerations" : 21005,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Talk show host",
		"consideration2" : "Call center representative",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Onion",
		"rt_response" : 21736,
		"rt_considerations" : 21636,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Potato",
		"consideration2" : "Corn",
		"consideration3" : "Onion",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "T-shirt",
		"rt_response" : 9937,
		"rt_considerations" : 16443,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Hoodies",
		"consideration2" : "Shoes",
		"consideration3" : "T-shirt",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 13509,
		"rt_considerations" : 13993,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Red Lobster",
		"rt_response" : 9153,
		"rt_considerations" : 12005,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration2" : "Applebees",
		"consideration3" : "Red Robin",
		"consideration4" : "Red Lobster",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 19126,
		"rt_considerations" : 13596,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Table",
		"consideration2" : "Curtains",
		"consideration3" : "Couch",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1A7HKFWGH77QH",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Kettle",
		"rt_response" : 14170,
		"rt_considerations" : 16598,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "slmnuj0b22ex",
		"consideration1" : "Coffee pot",
		"consideration2" : "Kettle",
		"consideration3" : "Microwave",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Cook",
		"rt_response" : 10405.759999994189,
		"rt_considerations" : 25452.18500000192,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Gatherer",
		"consideration2" : "Hunter",
		"consideration3" : "Prostitute",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Onions",
		"rt_response" : 5360.944999963976,
		"rt_considerations" : 14876.639999973122,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Celery",
		"consideration2" : "Onion",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 3695.8149999845773,
		"rt_considerations" : 6533.759999962058,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Table",
		"consideration3" : "Couch",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Eggs",
		"rt_response" : 16118.239999981597,
		"rt_considerations" : 13503.234999952838,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Beef",
		"consideration2" : "Corned Beef",
		"consideration3" : "Cereal",
		"consideration4" : "Banana",
		"consideration5" : "Eggs",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Underwear",
		"rt_response" : 4168.355000030715,
		"rt_considerations" : 6044.6349999983795,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Underwear",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 3668.0449999985285,
		"rt_considerations" : 6130.0199999823235,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Chilis",
		"consideration2" : "Applebees",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 6112.709999957588,
		"rt_considerations" : 8219.489999988582,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Toaster",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Oven",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 6465.910000028089,
		"rt_considerations" : 7439.620000019204,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "St Patricks Day",
		"consideration2" : "Halloween",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Christmas",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Giraffe",
		"rt_response" : 3786.354999989271,
		"rt_considerations" : 5382.464999973308,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Cheetah",
		"consideration3" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2HSCKH5NKN5LP",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 3066.125000012107,
		"rt_considerations" : 5822.370000008959,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "56llerpe07je",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 27424.71999999907,
		"rt_considerations" : 54691.389999999956,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "potato",
		"consideration2" : "carrot",
		"consideration3" : "broccoli",
		"consideration4" : "cauliflower",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "st. patricks day",
		"rt_response" : 19668.92000000007,
		"rt_considerations" : 20541.76500000176,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "st. patricks day",
		"consideration2" : "christmas",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 5447.220000001835,
		"rt_considerations" : 28778.95499999795,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "hockey",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "rabbit",
		"rt_response" : 31600.12000000279,
		"rt_considerations" : 30211.490000001533,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "rabbit",
		"consideration2" : "monkey",
		"consideration3" : "giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "alligator",
		"consideration5" : "mouse",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "omelets ",
		"rt_response" : 24569.190000001923,
		"rt_considerations" : 25006.68500000029,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "omelets ",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 16931.234999999986,
		"rt_considerations" : 13007.900000000547,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "waitress",
		"rt_response" : 9632.214999997814,
		"rt_considerations" : 30584.664999998524,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "waitress",
		"consideration2" : "customer service",
		"consideration3" : "secretary",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "wendys",
		"rt_response" : 7451.444999998785,
		"rt_considerations" : 18296.89000000141,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "wendys",
		"consideration2" : "popeyes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 12070.175000000745,
		"rt_considerations" : 21162.990000000747,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "hats",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A16335MOISDG1F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 8913.065000000643,
		"rt_considerations" : 22550.69999999972,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "o3ycb2lvwx4t",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "blender",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "prostitution",
		"rt_response" : 6960.140000039246,
		"rt_considerations" : 20974.49999995297,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "fisherman",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 14757.080000010319,
		"rt_considerations" : 42501.86499999836,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "platypus",
		"consideration3" : "Kangaroo",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 9444.82999999309,
		"rt_considerations" : 22954.575000039767,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "wendys",
		"rt_response" : 16384.130000020377,
		"rt_considerations" : 31612.370000046212,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "wendys",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "tgi fridays",
		"consideration4" : "ihop",
		"consideration5" : "chilis",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "sweater",
		"rt_response" : 8082.475000002887,
		"rt_considerations" : 15000.949999957811,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "jacket",
		"consideration2" : "sweater",
		"consideration3" : "t-shirt",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 7321.575000009034,
		"rt_considerations" : 12532.544999965467,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "banana",
		"consideration3" : "pea",
		"consideration4" : "carrot",
		"consideration5" : "onion",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "independence day",
		"rt_response" : 13616.674999997485,
		"rt_considerations" : 16409.11499998765,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "valentines day",
		"consideration2" : "christmas",
		"consideration3" : "independence day",
		"consideration4" : "memorial day",
		"consideration5" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 7572.685000021011,
		"rt_considerations" : 16767.004999972414,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "oven",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 9907.269999966957,
		"rt_considerations" : 8689.595000003465,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "waffles",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "bacon",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1R5W4RQZTROD8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "tennis",
		"rt_response" : 5890.214999963064,
		"rt_considerations" : 8566.319999983534,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "bu9no6ay223k",
		"consideration1" : "golf",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "basketball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Chair Leg",
		"rt_response" : 8107.589999999618,
		"rt_considerations" : 58838.064999989,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Chair Leg",
		"consideration2" : "Table Leg",
		"consideration3" : "Chair",
		"consideration4" : "Cabinet Drawer",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Track",
		"rt_response" : 8984.605000005104,
		"rt_considerations" : 33709.29500000784,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Track",
		"consideration2" : "Gymnastics",
		"consideration3" : "Football",
		"consideration4" : "Soccer",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Fruity Pebbles",
		"rt_response" : 19943.894999974873,
		"rt_considerations" : 33000.68000002648,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Fruity Pebbles",
		"consideration2" : "Blueberry French Toast",
		"consideration3" : "Blueberry Pancake",
		"consideration4" : "Waffles",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Panda",
		"rt_response" : 15684.81000000611,
		"rt_considerations" : 31844.29499998805,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Panda",
		"consideration2" : "Elephant",
		"consideration3" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration4" : "Lion",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Coffee Machine",
		"rt_response" : 24296.169999986887,
		"rt_considerations" : 29897.440000000643,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Coffee Machine",
		"consideration2" : "Blender",
		"consideration3" : "Toaster",
		"consideration4" : "Microwave",
		"consideration5" : "Oven",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Prostitution",
		"rt_response" : 13219.49499999755,
		"rt_considerations" : 31458.92500001355,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Prostitution",
		"consideration2" : "Farmer",
		"consideration3" : "Blacksmith",
		"consideration4" : "Guard",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Coat",
		"rt_response" : 9357.50499999267,
		"rt_considerations" : 16429.329999984475,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Coat",
		"consideration2" : "Pants",
		"consideration3" : "Shirt",
		"consideration4" : "Shoes",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Hardees",
		"rt_response" : 53018.70000001509,
		"rt_considerations" : 37979.92499999236,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Hardees",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Cucumber",
		"rt_response" : 21225.05999999703,
		"rt_considerations" : 18009.180000022752,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Cucumber",
		"consideration2" : "Corn On The Cob",
		"consideration3" : "Lettuce",
		"consideration4" : "Celery",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1J9Z2VOHTT1UZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Thanksgiving",
		"rt_response" : 10383.215000008931,
		"rt_considerations" : 19064.11000000662,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "v7k207ghl0h8",
		"consideration1" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "Halloween",
		"consideration4" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "vest",
		"rt_response" : 20440.27000013739,
		"rt_considerations" : 92814.26999997348,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "T-shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "pot",
		"rt_response" : 16084.125000052154,
		"rt_considerations" : 20631.744999904186,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "pan",
		"consideration2" : "kettle",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Independence day",
		"rt_response" : 39105.12500023469,
		"rt_considerations" : 33671.399999875575,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "Labor",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "capsicum",
		"rt_response" : 16562.994999811053,
		"rt_considerations" : 18820.985000114888,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "peppers",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "ping-pong",
		"rt_response" : 20751.64999999106,
		"rt_considerations" : 20948.95499991253,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "bed",
		"rt_response" : 10642.905000131577,
		"rt_considerations" : 15881.409999914467,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "sandwich",
		"rt_response" : 30479.305000044405,
		"rt_considerations" : 15511.39000011608,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 17162.490000016987,
		"rt_considerations" : 19090.900000184774,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration2" : "turtle",
		"consideration3" : "snake",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Chipotle",
		"rt_response" : 15931.705000344664,
		"rt_considerations" : 18816.815000027418,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANBWJZYU2A68T",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "front-desk",
		"rt_response" : 23179.465000052005,
		"rt_considerations" : 15759.254999924451,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Nepali",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Nepalese",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "jrbgr53tofyn",
		"consideration1" : "teaching",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 12345.14499999932,
		"rt_considerations" : 57950.21500000075,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration2" : "mixer",
		"consideration3" : "microwave",
		"consideration4" : "sink eradicator",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 7188.9049999990675,
		"rt_considerations" : 32670.084999999744,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "hockey",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "track",
		"consideration5" : "ping pong",
		"consideration6" : "tennis",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "bear",
		"rt_response" : 16302.639999999898,
		"rt_considerations" : 22030.399999999616,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "giraffe",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "tiger",
		"consideration5" : "bird",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 14345.175000000367,
		"rt_considerations" : 29075.290000000678,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "underwear",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "swim suit",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 7923.525000000169,
		"rt_considerations" : 25190.179999999586,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "bread",
		"consideration3" : "cheerios",
		"consideration4" : "yogurt",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "avocado",
		"rt_response" : 9009.094999999448,
		"rt_considerations" : 26384.86999999982,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "onion",
		"consideration4" : "madarin",
		"consideration5" : "orange",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teacher",
		"rt_response" : 13115.79499999975,
		"rt_considerations" : 50175.41499999969,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "production operator",
		"consideration2" : "engineer",
		"consideration3" : "farmer",
		"consideration4" : "fireman",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Mortons",
		"rt_response" : 12455.504999999888,
		"rt_considerations" : 34844.55999999953,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "Flemings",
		"consideration2" : "Carabbas",
		"consideration3" : "olive garden",
		"consideration4" : "chilis",
		"consideration5" : "chipolte",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "cart",
		"rt_response" : 13764.735000000626,
		"rt_considerations" : 27005.595000000554,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "desk",
		"consideration4" : "dresser",
		"consideration5" : "cabinent",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F1TBDHPYAAXT",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 14250.385000001173,
		"rt_considerations" : 36408.96499999869,
		"age" : 71,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "Engilsh",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "gj2r8n47l74c",
		"consideration1" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "Easter",
		"consideration3" : "4th of july",
		"consideration4" : "Mlk day",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Soccer",
		"rt_response" : 20484.32500002673,
		"rt_considerations" : 34696.43499999074,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Basketball",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Hockey",
		"consideration4" : "Tennis",
		"consideration5" : "Golf",
		"consideration6" : "Track",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Waffles",
		"rt_response" : 17127.994999988005,
		"rt_considerations" : 34602.8299999889,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "burrito",
		"consideration2" : "Eggs",
		"consideration3" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration4" : "Cereal",
		"consideration5" : "Oatmeal",
		"consideration6" : "Cinnamon Sticks",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Socks",
		"rt_response" : 13770.010000036564,
		"rt_considerations" : 33458.43500003684,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Underwear",
		"consideration2" : "Pants",
		"consideration3" : "Shirts",
		"consideration4" : "Jewelry",
		"consideration5" : "Gloves",
		"consideration6" : "Hats",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Cheesecake Factory",
		"rt_response" : 24491.924999980256,
		"rt_considerations" : 52972.409999987576,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "TGI Fridays",
		"consideration2" : "Ruby Tuesdays",
		"consideration3" : "Panda Express",
		"consideration4" : "Benigans",
		"consideration5" : "Red Lobster",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Tiger",
		"rt_response" : 9938.090000010561,
		"rt_considerations" : 22977.51000005519,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Zebra",
		"consideration2" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "Lion",
		"consideration4" : "Bird",
		"consideration5" : "Monkey",
		"consideration6" : "Fish",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Hunter",
		"rt_response" : 8525.629999989178,
		"rt_considerations" : 20306.739999970887,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Farmer",
		"consideration2" : "Baker",
		"consideration3" : "Warrior",
		"consideration4" : "Mother",
		"consideration5" : "Painter",
		"consideration6" : "Priest",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Corn",
		"rt_response" : 7154.049999953713,
		"rt_considerations" : 29261.03500003228,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Tomato",
		"consideration2" : "Pickle",
		"consideration3" : "Celery",
		"consideration4" : "Eggplant",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Loveseat",
		"rt_response" : 14740.685000026133,
		"rt_considerations" : 28352.439999987837,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Spittoon",
		"consideration2" : "Chair",
		"consideration3" : "Toiler",
		"consideration4" : "Bar",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Labor Day",
		"rt_response" : 8077.279999968596,
		"rt_considerations" : 18070.82000002265,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Veterans Day",
		"consideration2" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration3" : "Birthdays",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1W7I6FN183I8F",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Dish washer",
		"rt_response" : 7717.684999981429,
		"rt_considerations" : 28206.795000005513,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "6c6ta7987gqb",
		"consideration1" : "Stove",
		"consideration2" : "Oven",
		"consideration3" : "Microwave",
		"consideration4" : "Freezer",
		"consideration5" : "Fridge",
		"consideration6" : "Mixer",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 35734.69000000114,
		"rt_considerations" : 57370.77000000136,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration3" : "cereal",
		"consideration4" : "bacon",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "applebees",
		"rt_response" : 30627.739999999903,
		"rt_considerations" : 42496.67000000045,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "olive garden",
		"consideration3" : "pappasitos",
		"consideration4" : "mambos seafood",
		"consideration5" : "applebees",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jacket",
		"rt_response" : 14671.07500000202,
		"rt_considerations" : 23658.89999999854,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "jacket",
		"consideration2" : "shoes",
		"consideration3" : "shirt",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "hat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 9793.99999999808,
		"rt_considerations" : 24381.969999998575,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkeys",
		"rt_response" : 26273.574999999255,
		"rt_considerations" : 23006.454999998794,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "penguin",
		"consideration2" : "monkeys",
		"consideration3" : "dolphins",
		"consideration4" : "turtles",
		"consideration5" : "lions",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 6409.344999999972,
		"rt_considerations" : 24366.47499999887,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 9665.829999998095,
		"rt_considerations" : 20831.600000001315,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "couch",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 27297.469999997702,
		"rt_considerations" : 28984.21000000235,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "cucumber",
		"consideration3" : "pepper",
		"consideration4" : "corn",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "surgeon",
		"rt_response" : 13865.954999997513,
		"rt_considerations" : 20278.260000002803,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "surgeon",
		"consideration2" : "doctor",
		"consideration3" : "pilot",
		"consideration4" : "eye doctor",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F51C49T9A34D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years eve",
		"rt_response" : 8809.71500000311,
		"rt_considerations" : 20781.48500000313,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "dl9xmcowkqlc",
		"consideration1" : "new years eve",
		"consideration2" : "chirstmas",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Clockmaker",
		"rt_response" : 14870.380000000296,
		"rt_considerations" : 51837.93000000151,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Engineer",
		"consideration2" : "Surgeon",
		"consideration3" : "Pilot",
		"consideration4" : "Clockmaker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Duck",
		"rt_response" : 29269.57499999844,
		"rt_considerations" : 32269.58999999988,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Bear",
		"consideration3" : "Flamingo",
		"consideration4" : "Wallaby",
		"consideration5" : "Duck",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Hat",
		"rt_response" : 22157.639999997627,
		"rt_considerations" : 30837.824999998702,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Jeans",
		"consideration2" : "Shirt",
		"consideration3" : "Jacket",
		"consideration4" : "Shoes",
		"consideration5" : "Hat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Easter",
		"rt_response" : 23916.385000000446,
		"rt_considerations" : 40390.50999999745,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "New Years",
		"consideration3" : "St. Patricks",
		"consideration4" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration5" : "Easter",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Sink",
		"rt_response" : 18629.725000002538,
		"rt_considerations" : 26493.74000000168,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Stove",
		"consideration2" : "Refrigerator ",
		"consideration3" : "Sink",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Tables",
		"rt_response" : 26725.344999998924,
		"rt_considerations" : 27909.810000001045,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Couch",
		"consideration2" : "Chairs",
		"consideration3" : "Cabinets",
		"consideration4" : "Tables",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 18629.814999996568,
		"rt_considerations" : 21861.830000001588,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Bacon",
		"consideration2" : "Eggs",
		"consideration3" : "Toast",
		"consideration4" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Sweet Potato",
		"rt_response" : 52165.68499999994,
		"rt_considerations" : 24237.44500000251,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Tomato",
		"consideration2" : "Corn",
		"consideration3" : "Sweet Onion",
		"consideration4" : "Sweet Potato",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Wendys",
		"rt_response" : 13869.399999999616,
		"rt_considerations" : 37212.94499999925,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration4" : "Hardees",
		"consideration5" : "Wendys",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2KMHUYFMCXRJ9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Gymnastics",
		"rt_response" : 8973.759999997215,
		"rt_considerations" : 22133.154999999562,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "basbaxg7casv",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Ice Skating",
		"consideration3" : "Gymnastics",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "donuts",
		"rt_response" : 9478.139999999257,
		"rt_considerations" : 19741.21500000183,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "donuts",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "dolphin",
		"rt_response" : 11549.794999998994,
		"rt_considerations" : 14060.915000001842,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "gorilla",
		"consideration3" : "zebra",
		"consideration4" : "fish",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "jack in the box",
		"rt_response" : 5973.7999999997555,
		"rt_considerations" : 10749.05999999828,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 6101.774999999179,
		"rt_considerations" : 44677.1099999969,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "toilet",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years eve",
		"rt_response" : 22917.56499999974,
		"rt_considerations" : 14509.34000000052,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "radish",
		"rt_response" : 6669.774999998481,
		"rt_considerations" : 14844.984999999724,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "their first job after they graduate",
		"rt_response" : 231197.07000000196,
		"rt_considerations" : 7229.240000000573,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 4205.665000001318,
		"rt_considerations" : 8349.644999998389,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 5485.724999998638,
		"rt_considerations" : 8077.495000001392,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DUPRZSMU9W5R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "wedding dress",
		"rt_response" : 6262.220000000496,
		"rt_considerations" : 8940.995000000868,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "us american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "kqtgbbh8qb7n",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "underwear",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "The one where they are the happiest.",
		"rt_response" : 31712.87499999744,
		"rt_considerations" : 109436.76500002039,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "The one where they are the happiest.",
		"consideration2" : "The one that pays the best.",
		"consideration3" : "The one they have while they have a family to support.",
		"consideration4" : "The ones where they feel the most competent.",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Toast and jam",
		"rt_response" : 24594.275000010384,
		"rt_considerations" : 34538.57499998412,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "Sausages and eggs",
		"consideration2" : "Oatmeal",
		"consideration3" : "Yogurt",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Potato",
		"rt_response" : 15973.895000002813,
		"rt_considerations" : 19191.525000002002,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "spinach",
		"consideration2" : "lettuce",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Basketball",
		"rt_response" : 9922.669999999925,
		"rt_considerations" : 20881.064999994123,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "hockey",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 22165.37000000244,
		"rt_considerations" : 21363.470000011148,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "koala",
		"consideration4" : "zebra",
		"consideration5" : "camel",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 7990.140000008978,
		"rt_considerations" : 19781.760000012582,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 10818.445000011707,
		"rt_considerations" : 43054.18999999529,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "pants",
		"rt_response" : 8029.340000008233,
		"rt_considerations" : 18465.23000000161,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "pants",
		"consideration2" : "blouse",
		"consideration3" : "underwear",
		"consideration4" : "shoes",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 18076.044999994338,
		"rt_considerations" : 27622.730000002775,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "Applebees",
		"consideration2" : "McDonald",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AAASQIW3J32OL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Kwanzaa",
		"rt_response" : 23474.669999995967,
		"rt_considerations" : 22820.275000005495,
		"age" : 60,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "z2dhem2qfqqx",
		"consideration1" : "Kwanzaa",
		"consideration2" : "Easter",
		"consideration3" : "Christmas",
		"consideration4" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pepper",
		"rt_response" : 15518.874999979744,
		"rt_considerations" : 67432.25000001257,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "pepper",
		"consideration2" : "banana",
		"consideration3" : "apple",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of July",
		"rt_response" : 21930.135000002338,
		"rt_considerations" : 48586.34000000893,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "leather",
		"rt_response" : 20439.829999988433,
		"rt_considerations" : 35905.3899999999,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "fur",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "washer & dryer",
		"rt_response" : 19646.669999987353,
		"rt_considerations" : 23362.905000016326,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 17604.389999993145,
		"rt_considerations" : 34939.28500000038,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "ape",
		"consideration3" : "allegator",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "assorted fruit",
		"rt_response" : 30109.095000021625,
		"rt_considerations" : 22047.805000009248,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "egg",
		"consideration2" : "sasuage",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "microwave",
		"rt_response" : 17253.454999998212,
		"rt_considerations" : 34885.29999999446,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "toaster oven",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "red lobster",
		"rt_response" : 14343.209999991814,
		"rt_considerations" : 45094.329999992624,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "olive garden",
		"consideration2" : "outback",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "cahier",
		"rt_response" : 31484.660000016447,
		"rt_considerations" : 29422.164999996312,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "stocket",
		"consideration2" : "janitor",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A39IEKRAOTJTD7",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "baseball",
		"rt_response" : 10120.280000002822,
		"rt_considerations" : 31539.950000005774,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "0zf0f9952fyt",
		"consideration1" : "stickball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 15008.664999972098,
		"rt_considerations" : 74248.23500000639,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "carrots",
		"consideration2" : "yams",
		"consideration3" : "peas",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 10941.685000027064,
		"rt_considerations" : 59400.60499997344,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "retail worker",
		"rt_response" : 18678.335000004154,
		"rt_considerations" : 64429.84499997692,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "retail worker",
		"consideration2" : "food server",
		"consideration3" : "call center worker",
		"consideration4" : "call center worker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 11329.450000019278,
		"rt_considerations" : 36465.26000002632,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "mixer",
		"consideration3" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 17574.095000047237,
		"rt_considerations" : 40276.97499998612,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "penguin",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jacket",
		"rt_response" : 13827.174999983981,
		"rt_considerations" : 35095.86499998113,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "scarf",
		"consideration3" : "gloves",
		"consideration4" : "hat",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 10318.579999962822,
		"rt_considerations" : 28505.784999986645,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "Arbys",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years Eve",
		"rt_response" : 9957.640000036918,
		"rt_considerations" : 36331.635000009555,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "4th of July",
		"consideration4" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 9000.545000017155,
		"rt_considerations" : 26003.759999992326,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "bed",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A259UZJQOOVE4V",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 12243.705000029877,
		"rt_considerations" : 61529.5449999976,
		"age" : 59,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "0krwse53m2ml",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "yogurt with fruit",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "microwave",
		"rt_response" : 6151.215000019874,
		"rt_considerations" : 33959.79500003159,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration2" : "range",
		"consideration3" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "bra",
		"rt_response" : 23715.624999953434,
		"rt_considerations" : 35681.489999988116,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "underwear",
		"consideration2" : "slip",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "halloween",
		"rt_response" : 18247.18499998562,
		"rt_considerations" : 27103.605000011157,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "4th of july",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "ice skating",
		"rt_response" : 18255.790000024717,
		"rt_considerations" : 12520.200000028126,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potatoe",
		"rt_response" : 14251.225000014529,
		"rt_considerations" : 22091.314999968745,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "bacon (lol)",
		"consideration2" : "apple (lol)",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "housewife",
		"rt_response" : 13571.539999975357,
		"rt_considerations" : 19928.03000001004,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "stewardess",
		"consideration2" : "computer programmer",
		"consideration3" : "nurse",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "oatmeal",
		"rt_response" : 18208.359999989625,
		"rt_considerations" : 24318.97000002209,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "bacon",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "smoothie",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 16175.960000022314,
		"rt_considerations" : 21890.645000035875,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "taco bell",
		"consideration2" : "burger king",
		"consideration3" : "chick fil a",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "penguin",
		"rt_response" : 39207.075000042096,
		"rt_considerations" : 22467.004999984056,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "monkey",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "snake",
		"consideration4" : "rabbit",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2APG8MSLJ6G2K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "end table",
		"rt_response" : 26296.635000035167,
		"rt_considerations" : 16897.77999999933,
		"age" : 69,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "7ccsqp5s2xts",
		"consideration1" : "lamp",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "fridge",
		"rt_response" : 6630.23000000976,
		"rt_considerations" : 34973.8499999512,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "fridge",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 24819.699999992736,
		"rt_considerations" : 13289.024999947287,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "table",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "corn",
		"rt_response" : 7022.2950000315905,
		"rt_considerations" : 21070.82999998238,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "fruits",
		"consideration4" : "peppers",
		"consideration5" : "corn",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "bug",
		"rt_response" : 8725.219999963883,
		"rt_considerations" : 10125.445000012405,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "bug",
		"consideration2" : "snake",
		"consideration3" : "mammal",
		"consideration4" : "bird",
		"consideration5" : "bug",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "mma",
		"rt_response" : 13574.520000023767,
		"rt_considerations" : 13326.004999980796,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "mma",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "mma",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 3614.999999990687,
		"rt_considerations" : 5845.175000024028,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 4614.740000048187,
		"rt_considerations" : 10110.99999997532,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "4th of july",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "christmas",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "sales",
		"rt_response" : 9669.265000033192,
		"rt_considerations" : 20989.71499997424,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "sales",
		"consideration2" : "Customer service",
		"consideration3" : "suicide hotline agent",
		"consideration4" : "sales",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "checkers",
		"rt_response" : 4567.619999987073,
		"rt_considerations" : 5470.249999954831,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "checkers",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3PHU8OHA8PONE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "sausage",
		"rt_response" : 5541.139999986626,
		"rt_considerations" : 11782.705000019632,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "hyw2v8u82msy",
		"consideration1" : "sausage",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "avocado",
		"rt_response" : 19989.46499999147,
		"rt_considerations" : 59363.82500000764,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "pepper",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "KFC",
		"rt_response" : 40749.92999993265,
		"rt_considerations" : 84566.26999995206,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys ",
		"consideration3" : "Long John SIlvers ",
		"consideration4" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration5" : "Pizza Hut",
		"consideration6" : "CiCis Pizza",
		"consideration7" : "KFC",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Farming",
		"rt_response" : 22843.54000003077,
		"rt_considerations" : 28505.765000008978,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "prostitution",
		"consideration2" : "farming",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "gloves",
		"rt_response" : 10371.335000032559,
		"rt_considerations" : 19173.239999916404,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "watch",
		"consideration3" : "gloves",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St. patricks day",
		"rt_response" : 56098.31499995198,
		"rt_considerations" : 24593.025000067428,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "New Years ",
		"consideration2" : "halloween",
		"consideration3" : "St. Patricks day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 15041.779999970458,
		"rt_considerations" : 20756.099999998696,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "hockey",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "oatmeal",
		"rt_response" : 7536.094999988563,
		"rt_considerations" : 30005.10499998927,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 5877.975000068545,
		"rt_considerations" : 19387.890000012703,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "penguin",
		"rt_response" : 25733.954999945126,
		"rt_considerations" : 36132.25499994587,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "parrot",
		"consideration2" : "zebra",
		"consideration3" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration4" : "giraffe",
		"consideration5" : "snake",
		"consideration6" : "penguin",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3DS5B06ZCD3E3",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 6110.3649999713525,
		"rt_considerations" : 19549.979999894276,
		"age" : 45,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "36k3ua7s0tq7",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 15866,
		"rt_considerations" : 67913,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration2" : "Fridays",
		"consideration3" : "Applebees",
		"consideration4" : "Dennys",
		"consideration5" : "Burger King",
		"consideration6" : "Wendys",
		"consideration7" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration8" : "KFC"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "office chair",
		"rt_response" : 11612,
		"rt_considerations" : 79069,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "desk",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "kitchen chair",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "prairie dog",
		"rt_response" : 17204,
		"rt_considerations" : 28572,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "zebra",
		"consideration3" : "polar bear",
		"consideration4" : "monkey",
		"consideration5" : "giraffe",
		"consideration6" : "camel",
		"consideration7" : "peacock",
		"consideration8" : "penguin"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 14885,
		"rt_considerations" : 54883,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "carrot",
		"consideration3" : "broccoli",
		"consideration4" : "brussel sprouts",
		"consideration5" : "celery",
		"consideration6" : "spinach",
		"consideration7" : "lettuce",
		"consideration8" : "asparagus"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "prostitute",
		"rt_response" : 13724,
		"rt_considerations" : 45372,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "lawyer",
		"consideration2" : "cop",
		"consideration3" : "firefighter",
		"consideration4" : "soldier",
		"consideration5" : "sales",
		"consideration6" : "banker",
		"consideration7" : "hit man",
		"consideration8" : "hunter"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Presidents Day",
		"rt_response" : 12154,
		"rt_considerations" : 59877,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "Independence Day",
		"consideration2" : "Memorial Day",
		"consideration3" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration4" : "Halloween",
		"consideration5" : "MLK Day",
		"consideration6" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration7" : "New Years",
		"consideration8" : "Columbus Day"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Track",
		"rt_response" : 10253,
		"rt_considerations" : 32517,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Soccer",
		"consideration4" : "Hockey",
		"consideration5" : "Basketball",
		"consideration6" : "Polo",
		"consideration7" : "Swimming",
		"consideration8" : "Pole Vault"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 5764,
		"rt_considerations" : 44539,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "Toaster",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Refridgerator",
		"consideration4" : "Air Fryer",
		"consideration5" : "Coffee Pot",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 17323,
		"rt_considerations" : 23836,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "jacket",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "hat",
		"consideration6" : "gloves",
		"consideration7" : "nylons",
		"consideration8" : "shoes"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MYPYBVHX7FQ2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 10269,
		"rt_considerations" : 39375,
		"age" : 50,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "dcvkejcbes6a",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "sausage",
		"consideration3" : "cereal",
		"consideration4" : "poptarts",
		"consideration5" : "hash browns",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Rowing",
		"rt_response" : 12142.800000001444,
		"rt_considerations" : 35002.77500000084,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Hockey",
		"consideration3" : "Soccer",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Sugary Breakfast Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 29490.065000001778,
		"rt_considerations" : 43103.814999998576,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Sugary Breakfast Cereal",
		"consideration2" : "English Muffins",
		"consideration3" : "Bagels",
		"consideration4" : "Packaged oatmeal",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Belt",
		"rt_response" : 14842.755000001489,
		"rt_considerations" : 32344.434999999066,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Jeans",
		"consideration2" : "Jacket",
		"consideration3" : "Tie",
		"consideration4" : "Dress shoes",
		"consideration5" : "Belt",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Call Center Operator",
		"rt_response" : 19708.569999998872,
		"rt_considerations" : 39330.37999999942,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Call Center Operator",
		"consideration2" : "CEO ",
		"consideration3" : "Restaurant Manager",
		"consideration4" : "Lawyer",
		"consideration5" : "Professor",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Pumpkin",
		"rt_response" : 17756.93500000122,
		"rt_considerations" : 52937.00499999977,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Bell Peppers",
		"consideration2" : "Packaged broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "Tomatoes",
		"consideration4" : "Pumpkin",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Foot stool",
		"rt_response" : 18872.3100000025,
		"rt_considerations" : 33073.29999999999,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Lawn chair",
		"consideration2" : "Park bench",
		"consideration3" : "Bar stool",
		"consideration4" : "Ottoman",
		"consideration5" : "Foot stool",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Arbor Day",
		"rt_response" : 12698.87000000017,
		"rt_considerations" : 54629.4149999994,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration2" : "Easter",
		"consideration3" : "Presidents Day",
		"consideration4" : "Columbus Day",
		"consideration5" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration6" : "Arbor Day",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Blender",
		"rt_response" : 31477.45500000019,
		"rt_considerations" : 50017.82000000088,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Wooden spatula",
		"consideration2" : "Toaster oven",
		"consideration3" : "Mixer",
		"consideration4" : "Dishes",
		"consideration5" : "Blender",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "hippopotamus",
		"rt_response" : 11909.589999999269,
		"rt_considerations" : 24823.365000000224,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "Zebra",
		"consideration4" : "Anaconda",
		"consideration5" : "Wolf",
		"consideration6" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11LL3J3YSXB4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 32685.289999997593,
		"rt_considerations" : 16254.640000002808,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "572o9ubm4d4u",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "Chick-Fil-A",
		"consideration3" : "Sonic",
		"consideration4" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 17189.770000055432,
		"rt_considerations" : 22852.465000003576,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Basketball",
		"consideration2" : "Tennis",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 13013.199999928474,
		"rt_considerations" : 20510.675000026822,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Air Fryer",
		"consideration2" : "Stovetop",
		"consideration3" : "Slow Cooker",
		"consideration4" : "Oven",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Peppers",
		"rt_response" : 14284.979999996722,
		"rt_considerations" : 17971.354999928735,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Carrots",
		"consideration2" : "Cauliflower",
		"consideration3" : "Peppers",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 11742.310000001453,
		"rt_considerations" : 34176.035000011325,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Oatmeal ",
		"consideration2" : "Cereal",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Penguin",
		"rt_response" : 19982.829999993555,
		"rt_considerations" : 14388.83499999065,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration2" : "Lion",
		"consideration3" : "Sloth",
		"consideration4" : "Penguin",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Chair",
		"rt_response" : 4005.339999916032,
		"rt_considerations" : 12508.39500001166,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Couch",
		"consideration2" : "Chair",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Pilot",
		"rt_response" : 16148.419999983162,
		"rt_considerations" : 15326.935000019148,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Air traffic Controller",
		"consideration2" : "Driver",
		"consideration3" : "Pilot",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Bra",
		"rt_response" : 4979.300000006333,
		"rt_considerations" : 13391.405000002123,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "T-shirt",
		"consideration2" : "underwear",
		"consideration3" : "Bra",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Olive Garden",
		"rt_response" : 17250.63499994576,
		"rt_considerations" : 20762.91500008665,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Cheesecake Factory",
		"consideration2" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration3" : "Outback",
		"consideration4" : "Chilis",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2WC2NO555XU3J",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Preisdents Day",
		"rt_response" : 11749.504999956116,
		"rt_considerations" : 16676.33500008378,
		"age" : 27,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English ",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "dkfsgfyv4a2q",
		"consideration1" : "Easter ",
		"consideration2" : "Valentines",
		"consideration3" : "Presidents Day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Corn",
		"rt_response" : 6015.63499995973,
		"rt_considerations" : 49417.66000003554,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "Broccoli",
		"consideration2" : "Carrots",
		"consideration3" : "Asparagus ",
		"consideration4" : "Beets",
		"consideration5" : "Potatoes",
		"consideration6" : "Yams",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 12578.080000006594,
		"rt_considerations" : 47840.255000046454,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "dish washer",
		"consideration2" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration3" : "food processer",
		"consideration4" : "sink",
		"consideration5" : "garbage disposal",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "tank tops",
		"rt_response" : 25675.010000006296,
		"rt_considerations" : 35130.19499997608,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "coats",
		"consideration2" : "underwear",
		"consideration3" : "bras",
		"consideration4" : "tshirts",
		"consideration5" : "dress shirts",
		"consideration6" : "slacks",
		"consideration7" : "suit jackets",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "cashier",
		"rt_response" : 18260.145000065677,
		"rt_considerations" : 28914.484999957494,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "nurse",
		"consideration2" : "fireman",
		"consideration3" : "emt",
		"consideration4" : "computer programer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 20458.169999998063,
		"rt_considerations" : 48178.17000008654,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "mma",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "track",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "table leg",
		"rt_response" : 9194.599999929778,
		"rt_considerations" : 19267.324999906123,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "lamp",
		"consideration2" : "desk",
		"consideration3" : "chair",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Chilis",
		"rt_response" : 8971.445000031963,
		"rt_considerations" : 37618.17999999039,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "TGI Fridays",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "Wendys",
		"consideration5" : "Outback",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Omelet",
		"rt_response" : 8316.56499998644,
		"rt_considerations" : 31763.079999946058,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration3" : "fruit salad",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "penguin",
		"rt_response" : 43491.39999994077,
		"rt_considerations" : 21042.995000025257,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "Puffin",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1M64R8HPYNNZA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of july",
		"rt_response" : 10684.50499989558,
		"rt_considerations" : 39537.21500001848,
		"age" : 43,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "ghr7sx1nbdvb",
		"consideration1" : "labor day",
		"consideration2" : "columbus day",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "St Patricks day",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Burger King",
		"rt_response" : 12116.184999991674,
		"rt_considerations" : 54264.25000000745,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Mc Donalds",
		"consideration2" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration3" : "KFC",
		"consideration4" : "Jack in the Box",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of July",
		"rt_response" : 15230.299999995623,
		"rt_considerations" : 59493.51499998011,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "New Years",
		"consideration3" : "Presidents Day",
		"consideration4" : "Memorial Day",
		"consideration5" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration6" : "Veterans Day",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Tea Kettle",
		"rt_response" : 12862.46500001289,
		"rt_considerations" : 62881.52499997523,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Freezer",
		"consideration2" : "Fridge",
		"consideration3" : "Can Opener",
		"consideration4" : "Toaster",
		"consideration5" : "Oven",
		"consideration6" : "Microwave",
		"consideration7" : "Coffee Maker",
		"consideration8" : "Dishwasher"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Chair",
		"rt_response" : 52126.40000000829,
		"rt_considerations" : 47852.60499996366,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Sofa",
		"consideration2" : "Recliner",
		"consideration3" : "Ottoman",
		"consideration4" : "Bench",
		"consideration5" : "Bed",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Tomato",
		"rt_response" : 16158.144999993965,
		"rt_considerations" : 43274.83499998925,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Onion",
		"consideration2" : "Lettuce",
		"consideration3" : "Celery",
		"consideration4" : "Cabbage",
		"consideration5" : "Raddish",
		"consideration6" : "Squash",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 8015.52499999525,
		"rt_considerations" : 62500.020000035875,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Zebra",
		"consideration2" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration4" : "Rhinoceros",
		"consideration5" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration6" : "lion",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Fruit Loops",
		"rt_response" : 13550.435000041034,
		"rt_considerations" : 55734.45500002708,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Eggs",
		"consideration2" : "Quiche",
		"consideration3" : "chorizo",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Jacket",
		"rt_response" : 7214.834999991581,
		"rt_considerations" : 34703.994999988936,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "hat",
		"consideration3" : "scarf",
		"consideration4" : "shirt",
		"consideration5" : "boots",
		"consideration6" : "shoes",
		"consideration7" : "gloves",
		"consideration8" : "pants"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Baseball",
		"rt_response" : 15312.5,
		"rt_considerations" : 42362.220000009984,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Basketball",
		"consideration2" : "Football",
		"consideration3" : "Golf",
		"consideration4" : "Volleyball",
		"consideration5" : "Soccer",
		"consideration6" : "Tennis",
		"consideration7" : "Softball",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A22ZYDQ7VRH6EL",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Food Service",
		"rt_response" : 18014.169999980368,
		"rt_considerations" : 37805.29499996919,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "zxl71ncq9qky",
		"consideration1" : "Customer Service",
		"consideration2" : "Medical",
		"consideration3" : "Sales",
		"consideration4" : "Construction",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "cloth",
		"rt_response" : 8322.580000036396,
		"rt_considerations" : 138843.66999997292,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "cloth",
		"consideration2" : "leather",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "oatmeal",
		"rt_response" : 7146.485000033863,
		"rt_considerations" : 13884.77000000421,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jeans",
		"rt_response" : 5682.89499997627,
		"rt_considerations" : 18133.999999961816,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "jeans",
		"consideration2" : "pajamas",
		"consideration3" : "shirts",
		"consideration4" : "boxers",
		"consideration5" : "socks",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "chipotle",
		"rt_response" : 6996.8349999981,
		"rt_considerations" : 19323.970000026748,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "chipotle",
		"consideration2" : "olive garden",
		"consideration3" : "burger king",
		"consideration4" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 7147.239999962039,
		"rt_considerations" : 13635.950000025332,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "apple",
		"rt_response" : 5219.509999966249,
		"rt_considerations" : 11326.230000006035,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "apple",
		"consideration2" : "pepper",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 6017.824999988079,
		"rt_considerations" : 17549.48000004515,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "basketball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "microwave",
		"rt_response" : 6154.824999975972,
		"rt_considerations" : 12083.574999938719,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "toaster",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "hunter",
		"rt_response" : 8011.670000036247,
		"rt_considerations" : 16325.275000068359,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "hunter",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AK1GE19RT3PK6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "thanksgiving",
		"rt_response" : 8364.150000037625,
		"rt_considerations" : 12349.73000001628,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "txe8l8q2b71t",
		"consideration1" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "halloween",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 46745,
		"rt_considerations" : 82632,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "peppers",
		"consideration2" : "radishes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "halloween",
		"rt_response" : 51775,
		"rt_considerations" : 34147,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "crock pot",
		"rt_response" : 9752,
		"rt_considerations" : 25472,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "crock pot",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Pilot",
		"rt_response" : 21168,
		"rt_considerations" : 40539,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "Pilot",
		"consideration2" : "air traffic controller",
		"consideration3" : "police officer",
		"consideration4" : "firefighter",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 11438,
		"rt_considerations" : 24540,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "shirts",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "wooden table",
		"rt_response" : 24084,
		"rt_considerations" : 25649,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "wooden table",
		"consideration2" : "chairs",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 21155,
		"rt_considerations" : 22589,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Taco Bell",
		"rt_response" : 58495,
		"rt_considerations" : 45697,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "Taco bell",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "wendys",
		"consideration4" : "Dominos",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "alligator",
		"rt_response" : 72828,
		"rt_considerations" : 25910,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "alligator",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "monkey",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A19L8SNH73AX1Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "breakfast steak",
		"rt_response" : 67160,
		"rt_considerations" : 22189,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "US",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "8sj5j5v4gvm4",
		"consideration1" : "breakfast steak",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "waffles",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 7602.840000001379,
		"rt_considerations" : 17931.884999999966,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "ottoman",
		"consideration3" : "armchair",
		"consideration4" : "table",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "burger king",
		"rt_response" : 5321.294999999736,
		"rt_considerations" : 12924.26499999965,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "applebees",
		"consideration3" : "chilis",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "bras",
		"rt_response" : 7522.914999999557,
		"rt_considerations" : 13089.884999999413,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hurdling",
		"rt_response" : 18908.44499999912,
		"rt_considerations" : 18640.25000000038,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "swimming",
		"consideration2" : "running",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "polo",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "froot loops",
		"rt_response" : 4750.889999999345,
		"rt_considerations" : 7083.420000000842,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "apple",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "jewelry repair",
		"rt_response" : 12806.5399999996,
		"rt_considerations" : 22481.154999999475,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "astronomer",
		"consideration2" : "construction worker",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "plumber",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "avocado",
		"rt_response" : 292432.5600000011,
		"rt_considerations" : 15089.299999999697,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "cucumber",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "zucchini",
		"consideration4" : "watermelon",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years",
		"rt_response" : 98291.25999999995,
		"rt_considerations" : 5813.824999999255,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 4365.889999999083,
		"rt_considerations" : 9981.949999999371,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1VMPZVVVZUCS4",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "spatula",
		"rt_response" : 11237.515000000596,
		"rt_considerations" : 17108.22000000009,
		"age" : 35,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Other",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "qy8xx5hl77b7",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "fridge",
		"consideration3" : "glass",
		"consideration4" : "faucet",
		"consideration5" : "whisk",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Basketball because it requires the most active participation amongst teammates to be successful",
		"rt_response" : 43462.78000000166,
		"rt_considerations" : 37770.02499999071,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "soccer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "giraffe",
		"rt_response" : 11081.690000006347,
		"rt_considerations" : 30637.665000002016,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "penguin",
		"consideration4" : "giraffe",
		"consideration5" : "zebra",
		"consideration6" : "monkey",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Thanksgiving because I dont like turkey or stuffing",
		"rt_response" : 36004.52499999665,
		"rt_considerations" : 35746.05000000156,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Hanukkah",
		"consideration4" : "4th of July",
		"consideration5" : "Halloween",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "corn",
		"rt_response" : 68546.34000000078,
		"rt_considerations" : 33121.10499999835,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "peas",
		"consideration2" : "green beans",
		"consideration3" : "squash",
		"consideration4" : "corn",
		"consideration5" : "asparagus",
		"consideration6" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration7" : "broccoli",
		"consideration8" : "cauliflower"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 6992.740000001504,
		"rt_considerations" : 35097.789999999804,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "microwave",
		"consideration5" : "blender",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 6932.950000002165,
		"rt_considerations" : 21168.45500000636,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "shirts",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "dresses",
		"consideration4" : "scarves",
		"consideration5" : "shorts",
		"consideration6" : "shoes",
		"consideration7" : "jackets",
		"consideration8" : "socks"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "sales",
		"rt_response" : 7524.19500000542,
		"rt_considerations" : 24414.77999999188,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "doctor",
		"consideration2" : "lawyer",
		"consideration3" : "police officer",
		"consideration4" : "mailman",
		"consideration5" : "server",
		"consideration6" : "janitor",
		"consideration7" : "electrician",
		"consideration8" : "teacher"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 14500.430000000051,
		"rt_considerations" : 41614.749999993364,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "Panda Express",
		"consideration3" : "Panera",
		"consideration4" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration5" : "Arbys ",
		"consideration6" : "Wendys",
		"consideration7" : "Subway",
		"consideration8" : "Qdoba"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "omelet",
		"rt_response" : 7548.969999988913,
		"rt_considerations" : 69734.50999999477,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "french toast",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration4" : "steak and eggs",
		"consideration5" : "omelette",
		"consideration6" : "toast",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A11BACV6DY5S8M",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 25160.089999990305,
		"rt_considerations" : 59731.07000000891,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "US American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "c8qf8t2o753j",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "desk",
		"consideration4" : "recliner",
		"consideration5" : "end table",
		"consideration6" : "lamp",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 13291.815000004135,
		"rt_considerations" : 67532.88000001339,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "wendys",
		"consideration3" : "kfc",
		"consideration4" : "del taco",
		"consideration5" : "chic fil a",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "handbag",
		"rt_response" : 107639.81500000227,
		"rt_considerations" : 55125.60500000836,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "wallet",
		"consideration2" : "scarf",
		"consideration3" : "jeans",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Halloween",
		"rt_response" : 26255.315000016708,
		"rt_considerations" : 29801.854999997886,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "Kwanza",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "beans",
		"rt_response" : 43321.70999998925,
		"rt_considerations" : 29583.055000024615,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "potatoes",
		"consideration2" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration3" : "rhubarb",
		"consideration4" : "celery",
		"consideration5" : "turnips",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "cheering",
		"rt_response" : 9057.28999999701,
		"rt_considerations" : 31307.124999992084,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "hockey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "mixer",
		"rt_response" : 15377.000000007683,
		"rt_considerations" : 22987.705000006827,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "toaster",
		"consideration3" : "oven",
		"consideration4" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "coffee table",
		"rt_response" : 11744.054999988293,
		"rt_considerations" : 22464.365000021644,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "bookcase",
		"consideration3" : "sofa",
		"consideration4" : "bed",
		"consideration5" : "end table",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 23459.665000002133,
		"rt_considerations" : 20894.425000005867,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "coffee",
		"consideration2" : "bagel",
		"consideration3" : "english muffin",
		"consideration4" : "eggs",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 26180.865000002086,
		"rt_considerations" : 26691.339999990305,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "bear",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2YTQDLACTLIBA",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "janitor",
		"rt_response" : 26166.185000009136,
		"rt_considerations" : 18728.0449999962,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "9v0fckx97q0e",
		"consideration1" : "doctor",
		"consideration2" : "lawyer",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "construction worker",
		"rt_response" : 14597.694999996806,
		"rt_considerations" : 18560.929999999702,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "president",
		"consideration2" : "police officer",
		"consideration3" : "janitor",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "corn",
		"rt_response" : 11042.654999997467,
		"rt_considerations" : 14275.090000002878,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "carrots",
		"consideration2" : "broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "cabbage",
		"consideration4" : "eggplant",
		"consideration5" : "tomato",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 5599.050000004354,
		"rt_considerations" : 13320.97000000067,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "shirts",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "sweater",
		"consideration4" : "coat",
		"consideration5" : "jacket",
		"consideration6" : "socks",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 8416.064999997616,
		"rt_considerations" : 12222.890000004554,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "monkey",
		"consideration5" : "giraffe",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "omlette",
		"rt_response" : 12618.6650000019,
		"rt_considerations" : 17513.92499999923,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "waffles",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "toast",
		"consideration5" : "pancakes",
		"consideration6" : "crepes",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Olive Garden",
		"rt_response" : 7944.504999999423,
		"rt_considerations" : 21473.205000002054,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "Chilis",
		"consideration2" : "Applebees",
		"consideration3" : "Fridays",
		"consideration4" : "Outback",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "golf",
		"rt_response" : 8975.265000000829,
		"rt_considerations" : 19187.200000000303,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "tennis",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "football",
		"consideration5" : "cricket",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St. Patricks Day",
		"rt_response" : 7560.479999999981,
		"rt_considerations" : 12405.100000003586,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "New Years",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 21976.279999995255,
		"rt_considerations" : 11153.299999998068,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "desk",
		"consideration5" : "television",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Z8VN97YAD6XB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 2713.909999998519,
		"rt_considerations" : 13318.440000002738,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "oh9rb5dwbux0",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 23719.385000003967,
		"rt_considerations" : 87252.39999999758,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "tiger",
		"consideration5" : "bear",
		"consideration6" : "monkey",
		"consideration7" : "zebra",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Shirt",
		"rt_response" : 8353.559999959543,
		"rt_considerations" : 27474.83999998076,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "shoes",
		"consideration4" : "coat",
		"consideration5" : "socks",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "applebees",
		"rt_response" : 13161.759999988135,
		"rt_considerations" : 51200.09499997832,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "outback",
		"consideration3" : "red robin",
		"consideration4" : "olive garden",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years eve",
		"rt_response" : 6521.249999990687,
		"rt_considerations" : 41059.38499997137,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "New years eve",
		"consideration2" : "New years",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Halloween ",
		"consideration5" : "Christmas",
		"consideration6" : "4$th of July",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "end table",
		"rt_response" : 10181.33500003023,
		"rt_considerations" : 26555.590000003576,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "end table",
		"consideration2" : "coffee table",
		"consideration3" : "chair",
		"consideration4" : "couch",
		"consideration5" : "tv stand",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teacher",
		"rt_response" : 6634.265000000596,
		"rt_considerations" : 35462.674999958836,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "teacher",
		"consideration2" : "cashier",
		"consideration3" : "nurse",
		"consideration4" : "customer service",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 5987.429999979213,
		"rt_considerations" : 26518.945000017993,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "football",
		"consideration5" : "golf",
		"consideration6" : "basketball",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "biscuits and gravy",
		"rt_response" : 27559.19499997981,
		"rt_considerations" : 32255.315000016708,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "bacon",
		"consideration2" : "waffles",
		"consideration3" : "pancake",
		"consideration4" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration5" : "cereal",
		"consideration6" : "eggs",
		"consideration7" : "biscuits and gravy",
		"consideration8" : "sausage"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "broccoli ",
		"rt_response" : 35746.305000036955,
		"rt_considerations" : 26804.290000000037,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "broccoli ",
		"consideration2" : "spinach",
		"consideration3" : "carrot",
		"consideration4" : "beets",
		"consideration5" : "asparagus",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A37PUSY6CJ7TQ0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 13097.049999982119,
		"rt_considerations" : 24337.2049999889,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "Engish",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "ha53rnqw3enc",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "mixer",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "coffee pot",
		"consideration5" : "microwave",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 9726.829999999609,
		"rt_considerations" : 47068.844999997964,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "bear",
		"consideration4" : "elephant",
		"consideration5" : "giraffe",
		"consideration6" : "penguin",
		"consideration7" : "bird",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "doctor",
		"rt_response" : 7390.220000001136,
		"rt_considerations" : 40886.03000000148,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "receptionist",
		"consideration2" : "telemarketer",
		"consideration3" : "cashier",
		"consideration4" : "teacher",
		"consideration5" : "fast food worker",
		"consideration6" : "waitress",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "kfc",
		"rt_response" : 11621.759999998176,
		"rt_considerations" : 50253.27499999912,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "taco bell",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "bed",
		"rt_response" : 8366.219999999885,
		"rt_considerations" : 26725.545000001148,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "mattress",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "couch",
		"consideration4" : "chair",
		"consideration5" : "desktop",
		"consideration6" : "dresser",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirts",
		"rt_response" : 8918.020000000979,
		"rt_considerations" : 26797.61999999755,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "pants",
		"consideration2" : "jackets",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "sweatshirt",
		"consideration6" : "belt",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "baseball",
		"rt_response" : 8414.114999999583,
		"rt_considerations" : 19669.39999999886,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "hockey",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "basketball",
		"consideration5" : "soccer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Halloween",
		"rt_response" : 34470.29499999917,
		"rt_considerations" : 26909.240000000806,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "Easter",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "4th of July",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "cucumber",
		"rt_response" : 8477.949999996752,
		"rt_considerations" : 11902.17499999929,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "green bean",
		"consideration3" : "peas",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 18238.37999999884,
		"rt_considerations" : 18021.17999999976,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "toast",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "omlete",
		"consideration4" : "hash browns",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1CFMY4CEYOM8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "microwave",
		"rt_response" : 10861.829999998037,
		"rt_considerations" : 17477.61999999784,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "exz1koyza5as",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "coffee pot",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 8314.634999958798,
		"rt_considerations" : 41985.43000011705,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "sofa",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "sniper",
		"rt_response" : 8181.675000116229,
		"rt_considerations" : 28879.399999976158,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "sniper",
		"consideration2" : "pilot",
		"consideration3" : "police officer",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 6952.31999992393,
		"rt_considerations" : 22862.87000006996,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "banana",
		"consideration3" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 11388.46499985084,
		"rt_considerations" : 17929.079999914393,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "refrig",
		"consideration3" : "oven",
		"consideration4" : "micorwave",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 6514.900000067428,
		"rt_considerations" : 33541.510000126436,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "easter",
		"consideration3" : "halloween",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 4572.5600000005215,
		"rt_considerations" : 15583.949999883771,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "bear",
		"consideration4" : "monkey",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "baseball",
		"rt_response" : 4749.904999975115,
		"rt_considerations" : 21221.494999947026,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "basketball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrot",
		"rt_response" : 5443.094999995083,
		"rt_considerations" : 17522.325000027195,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "lettuce",
		"consideration3" : "spinach",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "gloves",
		"rt_response" : 8833.764999872074,
		"rt_considerations" : 17999.670000048354,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "gloves",
		"consideration2" : "pant",
		"consideration3" : "shirt",
		"consideration4" : "sock",
		"consideration5" : "shoe",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AGKCK081EU63R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "appleby",
		"rt_response" : 19247.81500012614,
		"rt_considerations" : 13646.060000173748,
		"age" : 55,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "jjart04kl3mr",
		"consideration1" : "appleby",
		"consideration2" : "wendy",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 5527.490000007674,
		"rt_considerations" : 32852.15000004973,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "Tiger",
		"consideration4" : "Bear",
		"consideration5" : "Whale",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 8489.560000016354,
		"rt_considerations" : 18987.160000018775,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Candy",
		"consideration2" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "Toast",
		"consideration4" : "Toast & Jam",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Blender",
		"rt_response" : 6253.350000013597,
		"rt_considerations" : 18063.934999983758,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Faucet",
		"consideration2" : "Toaster",
		"consideration3" : "Microwave",
		"consideration4" : "Oven",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 6623.3899999642745,
		"rt_considerations" : 21517.570000025444,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Subway",
		"consideration4" : "Panera Bread",
		"consideration5" : "Chic-Fil-A",
		"consideration6" : "Burger King",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Hoodie",
		"rt_response" : 7728.61000004923,
		"rt_considerations" : 24063.35000001127,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Shoes",
		"consideration2" : "Jacket",
		"consideration3" : "Pants",
		"consideration4" : "Socks",
		"consideration5" : "Shirt",
		"consideration6" : "Dresses",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Soccer",
		"rt_response" : 4264.670000004116,
		"rt_considerations" : 11923.660000029486,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Frisbee",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Accounting",
		"rt_response" : 6697.010000003502,
		"rt_considerations" : 17195.20499999635,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Writers",
		"consideration2" : "Doctors",
		"consideration3" : "Medicine",
		"consideration4" : "Pharmacists",
		"consideration5" : "Surgeons",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 8943.239999993239,
		"rt_considerations" : 17020.885000005364,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "Halloween",
		"consideration3" : "4th of July",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Carrots",
		"rt_response" : 23839.249999960884,
		"rt_considerations" : 9293.539999984205,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Corn",
		"consideration2" : "NA",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3KK5FKG3L0Q66",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Sofa",
		"rt_response" : 3834.4250000081956,
		"rt_considerations" : 10627.710000029765,
		"age" : 26,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "White / American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "799vyrmcnpeb",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Couch",
		"consideration3" : "Bed",
		"consideration4" : "Mattress",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Engineer",
		"rt_response" : 23837.365000043064,
		"rt_considerations" : 59954.66500008479,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "Doctor",
		"consideration2" : "Pilot",
		"consideration3" : "Taxi Driver",
		"consideration4" : "Athlete",
		"consideration5" : "Computer scientist",
		"consideration6" : "teacher",
		"consideration7" : "scientist",
		"consideration8" : "investment banker"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 6223.3450000640005,
		"rt_considerations" : 20907.174999825656,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "desk",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "couch",
		"consideration4" : "pillow",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 7691.334999864921,
		"rt_considerations" : 16009.789999807253,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "toaster",
		"consideration3" : "fridge",
		"consideration4" : "stove",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 4078.9150001946837,
		"rt_considerations" : 21688.30499984324,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "chick fil a ",
		"consideration2" : "burger king ",
		"consideration3" : "in n out",
		"consideration4" : "arbys",
		"consideration5" : "popeyes",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "hat",
		"rt_response" : 8880.570000037551,
		"rt_considerations" : 14561.319999862462,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "polo",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "shorts",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 3794.040000066161,
		"rt_considerations" : 31349.204999860376,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "hyena",
		"consideration4" : "giraffe",
		"consideration5" : "penguin",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 9878.78999998793,
		"rt_considerations" : 16911.654999945313,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "onion",
		"consideration3" : "spinach",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 9058.62500006333,
		"rt_considerations" : 16788.395000156015,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "golf",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New years eve",
		"rt_response" : 5717.9200001992285,
		"rt_considerations" : 19496.765000047162,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "valentines day",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AJZEXCH1TSUE1",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Beans",
		"rt_response" : 8933.229999849573,
		"rt_considerations" : 14108.840000117198,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "jwhs08rldbvj",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "toast",
		"consideration3" : "cereal",
		"consideration4" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 13531.619999994291,
		"rt_considerations" : 54774.47000000393,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "toaster oven",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "microwave",
		"consideration5" : "oven",
		"consideration6" : "drip coffee",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "armed chair",
		"rt_response" : 12944.539999996778,
		"rt_considerations" : 19721.900000004098,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrot",
		"rt_response" : 4399.299999990035,
		"rt_considerations" : 27313.085000001593,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "potato",
		"consideration2" : "sweet potato",
		"consideration3" : "onions",
		"consideration4" : "parsnips",
		"consideration5" : "radish",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "black angus",
		"rt_response" : 38433.95999999484,
		"rt_considerations" : 9810.510000010254,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "chilis",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years",
		"rt_response" : 6405.335000017658,
		"rt_considerations" : 26196.49999999092,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "halloween",
		"consideration4" : "4th of july",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 4569.955000013579,
		"rt_considerations" : 14813.37000001804,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "cricket",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "accountant",
		"rt_response" : 15434.009999997215,
		"rt_considerations" : 23641.949999990175,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "financial advisor",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cinnamon rolls",
		"rt_response" : 8877.084999985527,
		"rt_considerations" : 71757.76999999653,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "french toast",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 11446.185000007972,
		"rt_considerations" : 29882.760000007693,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "zebra",
		"consideration4" : "koala",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A337Y4X67PY4QI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "pajamas",
		"rt_response" : 8888.794999977108,
		"rt_considerations" : 257581.26999999513,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "j8757f5k9rjd",
		"consideration1" : "tshirts",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas ",
		"rt_response" : 13879,
		"rt_considerations" : 35218,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween candy",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas Eve fish",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving turkey",
		"consideration4" : "Easter eggs",
		"consideration5" : "Christmas ham",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 9656,
		"rt_considerations" : 22719,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "fridge",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "blender",
		"consideration4" : "dish washer",
		"consideration5" : "freezer",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 4670,
		"rt_considerations" : 21541,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "carrots",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "potatoes",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "platypus",
		"rt_response" : 14278,
		"rt_considerations" : 652144,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "bear",
		"consideration2" : "NA",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Ponderosa",
		"rt_response" : 23036,
		"rt_considerations" : 17784,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "Dennys",
		"consideration2" : "Arbys",
		"consideration3" : "Red Robin",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "sweater",
		"rt_response" : 7040,
		"rt_considerations" : 13207,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "coat",
		"consideration2" : "jeans",
		"consideration3" : "scarf",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "quiche",
		"rt_response" : 7570,
		"rt_considerations" : 12583,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "bacon",
		"consideration3" : "orange juice",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 8129,
		"rt_considerations" : 16560,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "vase",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "coat rack",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 15699,
		"rt_considerations" : 13451,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "rugby",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "golf",
		"consideration4" : "polo",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1FKRZKU1H9YFC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teaching",
		"rt_response" : 5720,
		"rt_considerations" : 15456,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "PhD",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "20c5rh660kwn",
		"consideration1" : "firefighter",
		"consideration2" : "cop",
		"consideration3" : "doctor",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "jcouch",
		"rt_response" : 3956.664999946952,
		"rt_considerations" : 60078.664999920875,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "mattress",
		"consideration3" : "chair",
		"consideration4" : "coffee table",
		"consideration5" : "rug",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 6237.935000099242,
		"rt_considerations" : 35784.14499992505,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "elephant",
		"consideration5" : "zebra",
		"consideration6" : "bull",
		"consideration7" : "cow",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "valentines day",
		"rt_response" : 7407.729999860749,
		"rt_considerations" : 28043.884999817237,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "columbus day",
		"consideration2" : "labor day",
		"consideration3" : "president day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds ",
		"rt_response" : 19496.269999770448,
		"rt_considerations" : 29870.929999975488,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "taco bell",
		"consideration3" : "wendys",
		"consideration4" : "kfc",
		"consideration5" : "arbys",
		"consideration6" : "subway",
		"consideration7" : "chikfila",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 50852.124999975786,
		"rt_considerations" : 77095.49500001594,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "soccer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "sales",
		"rt_response" : 4457.120000151917,
		"rt_considerations" : 72758.57999990694,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "lawyer",
		"consideration2" : "pastor",
		"consideration3" : "call center",
		"consideration4" : "agent",
		"consideration5" : "radio host",
		"consideration6" : "tv host",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 5087.720000185072,
		"rt_considerations" : 25366.369999945164,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "bacon",
		"consideration3" : "sausage ",
		"consideration4" : "pancakes",
		"consideration5" : "hashbrowns",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jeans",
		"rt_response" : 4156.829999992624,
		"rt_considerations" : 19224.195000017062,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "jeans",
		"consideration2" : "shoes",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "shirts",
		"consideration6" : "boxers",
		"consideration7" : "tank tops",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "corn",
		"rt_response" : 53215.46499989927,
		"rt_considerations" : 20987.535000080243,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "peas",
		"consideration2" : "corn",
		"consideration3" : "cabbage",
		"consideration4" : "broccoli",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3F8K7ZV8AX8UR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "heater",
		"rt_response" : 7960.279999999329,
		"rt_considerations" : 45571.8999998644,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "om1cjz1rxm1h",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "heater",
		"consideration3" : "fireplace",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years Eve",
		"rt_response" : 10951.319999992847,
		"rt_considerations" : 39541.99499997776,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "4th of July",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Christmas",
		"consideration5" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration6" : "Memorial Day",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "butterfly",
		"rt_response" : 25568.68000002578,
		"rt_considerations" : 27056.12000002293,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "frog",
		"consideration2" : "fish",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "tiger",
		"consideration5" : "monkey",
		"consideration6" : "zebra",
		"consideration7" : "elk",
		"consideration8" : "bird"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "TGI Fridays",
		"rt_response" : 11577.185000001919,
		"rt_considerations" : 36634.640000003856,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration3" : "Mcdonalds",
		"consideration4" : "burger king",
		"consideration5" : "panera",
		"consideration6" : "panda express",
		"consideration7" : "outback",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 7241.624999966007,
		"rt_considerations" : 23851.67000000365,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "bacon",
		"consideration2" : "french toast",
		"consideration3" : "bagel",
		"consideration4" : "waffles",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 5385.3499999968335,
		"rt_considerations" : 15896.134999988135,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "nighstand",
		"consideration4" : "dresser",
		"consideration5" : "desk",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 9592.709999997169,
		"rt_considerations" : 20432.090000016615,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "pants",
		"consideration2" : "sneakers",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "hat",
		"consideration6" : "gloves",
		"consideration7" : "scarf",
		"consideration8" : "boots"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 8120.104999979958,
		"rt_considerations" : 23143.195000011474,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "basketball",
		"consideration5" : "baseball",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pumpkin",
		"rt_response" : 18486.629999999423,
		"rt_considerations" : 19378.23000003118,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "squash",
		"consideration2" : "apple",
		"consideration3" : "melon",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "coffee maker",
		"rt_response" : 10324.68499999959,
		"rt_considerations" : 15254.974999988917,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "crockpot",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A281Q8U3T9H7JS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "waitress",
		"rt_response" : 8963.829999964219,
		"rt_considerations" : 15872.220000019297,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "bh76zbkfc0km",
		"consideration1" : "bartneder",
		"consideration2" : "nurse",
		"consideration3" : "lawyer",
		"consideration4" : "sales",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 20292.09499998251,
		"rt_considerations" : 59984.73500000546,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "nightstand",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Thanksgiving",
		"rt_response" : 54190.30000001658,
		"rt_considerations" : 60632.234999968205,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "Thanksgiving ",
		"consideration2" : "Easter",
		"consideration3" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration4" : "4th of July ",
		"consideration5" : "Christmas ",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "cabbage",
		"rt_response" : 44389.824999962,
		"rt_considerations" : 78634.64499998372,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "tomatoes ",
		"consideration3" : "lettuce",
		"consideration4" : "cabbage",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "pilot ",
		"rt_response" : 9813.514999987092,
		"rt_considerations" : 25256.70500000706,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "pilot ",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer ",
		"rt_response" : 6622.670000011567,
		"rt_considerations" : 28090.204999956768,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "lacrosse ",
		"consideration4" : "baseball ",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 7132.935000001453,
		"rt_considerations" : 20923.575000022538,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Burger King",
		"rt_response" : 10237.665000022389,
		"rt_considerations" : 29521.535000007134,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds ",
		"consideration2" : "Burger King",
		"consideration3" : "Subway",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 7149.1550000500865,
		"rt_considerations" : 18152.414999960456,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "pancakes ",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "tee shirt ",
		"rt_response" : 8999.219999997877,
		"rt_considerations" : 18953.5400000168,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "jeans",
		"consideration2" : "coat",
		"consideration3" : "tee shirt ",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1561P9VVA3C1C",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 8348.669999977574,
		"rt_considerations" : 16507.115000043996,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "1fnbg47bdjg2",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "POTATOES",
		"rt_response" : 23902.529999999388,
		"rt_considerations" : 99844.99499999947,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "THOUGHT OF NO OTHER OPTIONS THAN POTATOES",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 44736.04999999952,
		"rt_considerations" : 59357.185000000754,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "monkey",
		"consideration2" : "zebra",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 38682.83499999961,
		"rt_considerations" : 32974.36999999994,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "boxing",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "boxing",
		"consideration5" : "hockey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "government",
		"rt_response" : 43744.15000000229,
		"rt_considerations" : 40677.43500000145,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "law enforcement",
		"consideration2" : "doctors",
		"consideration3" : "nurses",
		"consideration4" : "sales",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Arbys",
		"rt_response" : 36323.145000002114,
		"rt_considerations" : 42838.39500000252,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "chicken fillet",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of july",
		"rt_response" : 64804.57000000018,
		"rt_considerations" : 24327.864999999292,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "labor day",
		"consideration2" : "memorial day",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 43212.32500000042,
		"rt_considerations" : 36777.760000000824,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "furnace",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jackets",
		"rt_response" : 89764.6150000001,
		"rt_considerations" : 29887.070000000647,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "jeans",
		"consideration3" : "skirts",
		"consideration4" : "dresses",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "wooden",
		"rt_response" : 37190.33500000287,
		"rt_considerations" : 27308.945000000647,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "coach",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1QTXDVUDSAMG2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon, eggs, potatoes, toast",
		"rt_response" : 75223.46499999915,
		"rt_considerations" : 26050.87499999709,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "913f5kcep26c",
		"consideration1" : "omelet",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 6037,
		"rt_considerations" : 32828,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrot",
		"rt_response" : 8690,
		"rt_considerations" : 26370,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "brocolli",
		"consideration2" : "potato",
		"consideration3" : "tomato",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 19380,
		"rt_considerations" : 25903,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "thanksgiving",
		"rt_response" : 8078,
		"rt_considerations" : 25591,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "new years",
		"consideration2" : "valentines",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 35409,
		"rt_considerations" : 21300,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "spoons",
		"consideration2" : "pots",
		"consideration3" : "plates",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "lawyer",
		"rt_response" : 7213,
		"rt_considerations" : 34076,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "doctor",
		"consideration2" : "lawyer",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 5330,
		"rt_considerations" : 23536,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "monkey",
		"consideration4" : "bird",
		"consideration5" : "peaccock",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 6078,
		"rt_considerations" : 25111,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "applebees",
		"rt_response" : 8983,
		"rt_considerations" : 26295,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "burger king",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1D2ZSPIHOI23K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 9158,
		"rt_considerations" : 22621,
		"age" : 21,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "asia",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "8h3shelbs35a",
		"consideration1" : "pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "waffles",
		"consideration3" : "cereal",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "french toast",
		"rt_response" : 35381.84500002535,
		"rt_considerations" : 44938.75999999,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "waffles",
		"consideration3" : "french toast",
		"consideration4" : "pancakes",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 7614.480000047479,
		"rt_considerations" : 24792.13499999605,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "sofa",
		"consideration4" : "bed",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 10170.480000029784,
		"rt_considerations" : 38173.13499999,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "peppers",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "belt",
		"rt_response" : 14347.784999990836,
		"rt_considerations" : 24095.835000043735,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "belt",
		"consideration3" : "shirt",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "dress",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 10604.700000025332,
		"rt_considerations" : 30825.455000041984,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "hockey",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "tiger",
		"rt_response" : 16130.035000038333,
		"rt_considerations" : 574460.1849999744,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "wolf",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "taco bell",
		"rt_response" : 8092.790000024252,
		"rt_considerations" : 40794.20000000391,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "subway",
		"consideration2" : "taco bell",
		"consideration3" : "pizza hut",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 8405.1750000217,
		"rt_considerations" : 22521.094999974594,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of july",
		"rt_response" : 13388.985000026878,
		"rt_considerations" : 31091.69499995187,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "4th of july",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "new years",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A110JX7PI2TTSS",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "electrician",
		"rt_response" : 13680.464999983087,
		"rt_considerations" : 23758.71000002371,
		"age" : 54,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "qpppyycjhdl0",
		"consideration1" : "electrician",
		"consideration2" : "referee",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "bird",
		"rt_response" : 13247.27500003064,
		"rt_considerations" : 93617.62999999337,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "alligator",
		"consideration2" : "snake",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration5" : "bear",
		"consideration6" : "monkey",
		"consideration7" : "gorilla",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 8033.640000037849,
		"rt_considerations" : 26674.400000018068,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "belt",
		"rt_response" : 19849.694999982603,
		"rt_considerations" : 14634.64499998372,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "jacket",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "shirt",
		"consideration4" : "shoes",
		"consideration5" : "socks",
		"consideration6" : "underwear",
		"consideration7" : "hat",
		"consideration8" : "scarf"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "olive garden",
		"rt_response" : 63754.600000043865,
		"rt_considerations" : 62535.93000001274,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "red lobster",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "burger king",
		"consideration4" : "pizza hut",
		"consideration5" : "taco bell",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "mushroom",
		"rt_response" : 57903.87500001816,
		"rt_considerations" : 44141.35500002885,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "lettuce",
		"consideration2" : "cabbage",
		"consideration3" : "potato",
		"consideration4" : "tomato",
		"consideration5" : "onion",
		"consideration6" : "celery",
		"consideration7" : "peppers",
		"consideration8" : "broccoli"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 32382.165000017267,
		"rt_considerations" : 29073.89499997953,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "hashbrowns",
		"consideration3" : "sausage",
		"consideration4" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Independence Day",
		"rt_response" : 35550.09500001324,
		"rt_considerations" : 49678.86500002351,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "MLK Day",
		"consideration2" : "Kwanzaa",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "bed",
		"rt_response" : 10461.59500000067,
		"rt_considerations" : 21562.66500003403,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "manager",
		"rt_response" : 16990.699999965727,
		"rt_considerations" : 54598.10000000289,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "driver",
		"consideration2" : "delivery person",
		"consideration3" : "server (waiterwaitress)",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1BWS5AD2T4NIR",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 41496.19999999413,
		"rt_considerations" : 19605.979999992996,
		"age" : 36,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "8t6ss9rqp19y",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "skiing",
		"consideration6" : "football",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 12352.985000004992,
		"rt_considerations" : 47285.82499991171,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "sweet peas",
		"consideration2" : "carrots",
		"consideration3" : "corn",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "end table",
		"rt_response" : 65691.08500005677,
		"rt_considerations" : 28154.224999947473,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "lamp",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 10771.68000000529,
		"rt_considerations" : 29685.0450001657,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "churchs",
		"rt_response" : 18147.965000011027,
		"rt_considerations" : 23941.15999992937,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "popeyes",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 22386.66999991983,
		"rt_considerations" : 25234.235000098124,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 23682.615000056103,
		"rt_considerations" : 27099.854999920353,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "mole rat",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "snake",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 13133.705000160262,
		"rt_considerations" : 22067.659999942407,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "government",
		"rt_response" : 10774.324999889359,
		"rt_considerations" : 18697.244999930263,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "presidents day",
		"rt_response" : 15692.375000100583,
		"rt_considerations" : 26271.35999989696,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "labor day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1Y9395AXC1FS0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 5134.885000064969,
		"rt_considerations" : 15510.11999999173,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "Yes",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "united states",
		"nationality" : "american blak",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "d5qlax3zr0g9",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "kangaroo",
		"rt_response" : 90210,
		"rt_considerations" : 31569,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "bear",
		"consideration4" : "penguin",
		"consideration5" : "platypus",
		"consideration6" : "sloth",
		"consideration7" : "seal",
		"consideration8" : "kangaroo"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "coffee maker",
		"rt_response" : 14987,
		"rt_considerations" : 28166,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration2" : "electric kettle",
		"consideration3" : "stove",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Halloween",
		"rt_response" : 13099,
		"rt_considerations" : 27522,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "Easter",
		"consideration4" : "MLK Day",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "clergy",
		"rt_response" : 18942,
		"rt_considerations" : 42380,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "mailman",
		"consideration2" : "garbage man",
		"consideration3" : "politician",
		"consideration4" : "doctor",
		"consideration5" : "clergy",
		"consideration6" : "athlete",
		"consideration7" : "accountant",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 16471,
		"rt_considerations" : 18961,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "bacon",
		"consideration5" : "candy",
		"consideration6" : "sausage",
		"consideration7" : "toast",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 14332,
		"rt_considerations" : 15627,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "football",
		"consideration6" : "baseball",
		"consideration7" : "badminton",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Taco Bell",
		"rt_response" : 10231,
		"rt_considerations" : 28185,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration3" : "Jack in the Box",
		"consideration4" : "Burger King",
		"consideration5" : "KFC",
		"consideration6" : "Chick-fil-A",
		"consideration7" : "In-and-Out Burger",
		"consideration8" : "Wendys"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "earrings",
		"rt_response" : 17070,
		"rt_considerations" : 18493,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "ring",
		"consideration2" : "shoes",
		"consideration3" : "jacket",
		"consideration4" : "pants",
		"consideration5" : "belt",
		"consideration6" : "shirt",
		"consideration7" : "coat",
		"consideration8" : "earrings"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potatoes",
		"rt_response" : 12599,
		"rt_considerations" : 13854,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration2" : "potatoes",
		"consideration3" : "carrots",
		"consideration4" : "corn",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALDQRWYZ8KQ9A",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "table",
		"rt_response" : 14258,
		"rt_considerations" : 18670,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "fnjxmtxw5f3v",
		"consideration1" : "table",
		"consideration2" : "desk",
		"consideration3" : "couch",
		"consideration4" : "bureau",
		"consideration5" : "bed",
		"consideration6" : "chair",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "wendys",
		"rt_response" : 90543.34500000004,
		"rt_considerations" : 71937.50000000001,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "KFC",
		"consideration2" : "MCDONALDS",
		"consideration3" : "TOCO BELL",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "ACCOUNTANT",
		"rt_response" : 23855.70499999993,
		"rt_considerations" : 63455.894999999146,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "ENGINEER",
		"consideration2" : "SUVEYOR",
		"consideration3" : "POLICE OFFICER",
		"consideration4" : "ARMY",
		"consideration5" : "IT",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "CARROT",
		"rt_response" : 17602.720000000787,
		"rt_considerations" : 95796.95999999973,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "TOMATOES",
		"consideration2" : "POTATOES",
		"consideration3" : "LETTUCE",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "FOOOTBALL",
		"rt_response" : 13462.510000001232,
		"rt_considerations" : 133019.50500000024,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "SOCCER",
		"consideration2" : "BASKETBALL",
		"consideration3" : "HOCKEY",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "KNIFE",
		"rt_response" : 148503.929999999,
		"rt_considerations" : 53988.2850000012,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "BLENDER",
		"consideration2" : "COFFEE MAKER",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "EASTER",
		"rt_response" : 42412.20500000054,
		"rt_considerations" : 39761.435000000405,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "CHRISTMAX",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "CAMEL",
		"rt_response" : 21109.834999999264,
		"rt_considerations" : 50427.92500000005,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "ZEBRA",
		"consideration2" : "TIGER",
		"consideration3" : "HYENAS",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "SWEATER",
		"rt_response" : 18842.875000000233,
		"rt_considerations" : 29809.7149999995,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "SHIRT",
		"consideration2" : "BLOUSE",
		"consideration3" : "JEAN",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "CHIPS",
		"rt_response" : 37313.364999999874,
		"rt_considerations" : 40690.5900000002,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "CRISP",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QUAM5Y482D4U",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "CHAIR",
		"rt_response" : 10220.86999999918,
		"rt_considerations" : 33906.74000000022,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "q24kpyf0l4qq",
		"consideration1" : "TABLE",
		"consideration2" : "SHELF",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Coffee grinder",
		"rt_response" : 17376,
		"rt_considerations" : 124565,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "Refrigerator",
		"consideration3" : "Blender",
		"consideration4" : "Coffee grinder",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Ruths Chris Steakhouse",
		"rt_response" : 31209,
		"rt_considerations" : 17944,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Ruths Chris Steakhouse",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "basketball",
		"rt_response" : 34303,
		"rt_considerations" : 44194,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Soccer",
		"consideration2" : "Hockey",
		"consideration3" : "Baseball",
		"consideration4" : "Football",
		"consideration5" : "Basketball",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "fireplace poker",
		"rt_response" : 139004,
		"rt_considerations" : 50766,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Desk",
		"consideration2" : "Chair",
		"consideration3" : "Vase",
		"consideration4" : "Lamp",
		"consideration5" : "Fan",
		"consideration6" : "Fireplace poker",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "kale",
		"rt_response" : 82811,
		"rt_considerations" : 54395,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Banana",
		"consideration2" : "Grapefruit",
		"consideration3" : "Orange",
		"consideration4" : "Tomato",
		"consideration5" : "Broccoli",
		"consideration6" : "Kale",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "ring",
		"rt_response" : 30907,
		"rt_considerations" : 24825,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Wristwatch",
		"consideration2" : "Earring",
		"consideration3" : "Ring",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "chimpanzee",
		"rt_response" : 64965,
		"rt_considerations" : 61176,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration4" : "Harambe",
		"consideration5" : "Chimpanzee",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Bosss Day",
		"rt_response" : 64270,
		"rt_considerations" : 34975,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Presidents Day",
		"consideration2" : "Columbus Day",
		"consideration3" : "Secretarys Day",
		"consideration4" : "Bosss Day",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Prostitute",
		"rt_response" : 7972,
		"rt_considerations" : 12599,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Prostitute",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A10AVWALIHR4UQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Kopi luwak",
		"rt_response" : 87855,
		"rt_considerations" : 55019,
		"age" : 37,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States of America",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "ljms40jl38k8",
		"consideration1" : "Cereal",
		"consideration2" : "Blueberries",
		"consideration3" : "Protein shake",
		"consideration4" : "Breakfast bars",
		"consideration5" : "Coffee",
		"consideration6" : "Kopi luwak",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 12133.535000000848,
		"rt_considerations" : 68002.17999999948,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "bacon",
		"consideration4" : "sausage",
		"consideration5" : "biscuits",
		"consideration6" : "oat meal",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "rowing",
		"rt_response" : 22968.675000000047,
		"rt_considerations" : 39637.475000001345,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "rowing",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "soccer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 49545.16999999943,
		"rt_considerations" : 49549.25000000006,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "birth of Jesus",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 24284.034999998752,
		"rt_considerations" : 45273.740000000515,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration5" : "disposal",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "prostitution",
		"rt_response" : 17116.589999999618,
		"rt_considerations" : 62392.58000000159,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "prostitution",
		"consideration2" : "bookkeeping",
		"consideration3" : "carpentry",
		"consideration4" : "plumbing",
		"consideration5" : "auto mechanic",
		"consideration6" : "teacher",
		"consideration7" : "laborer",
		"consideration8" : "bricklayer"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peach",
		"rt_response" : 28258.209999999963,
		"rt_considerations" : 53484.85500000056,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "peach",
		"consideration2" : "strawberry",
		"consideration3" : "banana",
		"consideration4" : "apple",
		"consideration5" : "blueberry",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 23990.465000000782,
		"rt_considerations" : 36875.3800000014,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "monkey",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "elephant",
		"consideration4" : "lion",
		"consideration5" : "tiger",
		"consideration6" : "snake",
		"consideration7" : "duck",
		"consideration8" : "deer"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 15340.909999998985,
		"rt_considerations" : 51593.205000001006,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Burger King",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 11973.109999998938,
		"rt_considerations" : 56008.77000000037,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "stool",
		"consideration4" : "bed",
		"consideration5" : "dresser",
		"consideration6" : "chase lounge",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3AT9S1CF9QV4K",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 9715.024999999558,
		"rt_considerations" : 41069.55000000016,
		"age" : 79,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "zxnhk7j7j7r8",
		"consideration1" : "coat",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "hat",
		"consideration5" : "gloves",
		"consideration6" : "scarf",
		"consideration7" : "mittens",
		"consideration8" : "socks"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "mattress",
		"rt_response" : 4868,
		"rt_considerations" : 21780,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "chair",
		"consideration4" : "recliner",
		"consideration5" : "sofa",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 5997,
		"rt_considerations" : 26981,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration4" : "Easter",
		"consideration5" : "MLK Day",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 8502,
		"rt_considerations" : 26229,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "lettuce",
		"consideration3" : "tomato",
		"consideration4" : "kale",
		"consideration5" : "onions",
		"consideration6" : "potatoes",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 6900,
		"rt_considerations" : 18020,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "volleyball",
		"consideration4" : "swimming",
		"consideration5" : "track",
		"consideration6" : "equestrian",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "fast food worker",
		"rt_response" : 4981,
		"rt_considerations" : 21268,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "office worker",
		"consideration2" : "manager",
		"consideration3" : "caterer",
		"consideration4" : "warehouse worker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 35861,
		"rt_considerations" : 9180,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "zebra",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "otter",
		"consideration4" : "lion",
		"consideration5" : "tiger",
		"consideration6" : "bear",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "jacket",
		"rt_response" : 6997,
		"rt_considerations" : 18734,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "sweatshirt",
		"consideration2" : "sweater",
		"consideration3" : "t shirt",
		"consideration4" : "coat",
		"consideration5" : "pants",
		"consideration6" : "skirt",
		"consideration7" : "shorts",
		"consideration8" : "socks"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Taco Bell",
		"rt_response" : 32539,
		"rt_considerations" : 15013,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "in-n-out",
		"consideration3" : "chick fil a",
		"consideration4" : "burger king",
		"consideration5" : "subway",
		"consideration6" : "starbucks",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "burrito",
		"rt_response" : 4732,
		"rt_considerations" : 18758,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "pastry",
		"consideration3" : "pumpkin spice latte",
		"consideration4" : "muffin",
		"consideration5" : "breakfast bar",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3IDG9C18BCATK",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 9083,
		"rt_considerations" : 47069,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "qxfgdr5pud1k",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 8646.145000006072,
		"rt_considerations" : 63986.724999995204,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "Dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 13105.855000001611,
		"rt_considerations" : 51474.39499999746,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "Eggs",
		"consideration2" : "Cereal",
		"consideration3" : "Waffles",
		"consideration4" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration5" : "pancakes",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "tomato",
		"rt_response" : 28508.694999996806,
		"rt_considerations" : 58477.44999997667,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "peas",
		"consideration4" : "carrot",
		"consideration5" : "zucchini",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Hockey",
		"rt_response" : 10338.61999999499,
		"rt_considerations" : 50162.974999984726,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "golf",
		"consideration5" : "hockey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Doctor",
		"rt_response" : 14800.795000017388,
		"rt_considerations" : 46344.740000000456,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "Lawyer",
		"consideration2" : "cashier",
		"consideration3" : "accountant",
		"consideration4" : "construction",
		"consideration5" : "veterinarian ",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 20397.079999995185,
		"rt_considerations" : 71176.60999999498,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "hallowean",
		"consideration3" : "new years",
		"consideration4" : "valentines day",
		"consideration5" : "forth of july",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Zebra",
		"rt_response" : 15987.739999982296,
		"rt_considerations" : 31242.69000001368,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "monkey",
		"consideration4" : "turtle",
		"consideration5" : "zebra",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Jeans",
		"rt_response" : 6879.83499999973,
		"rt_considerations" : 34165.81999999471,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "hats",
		"consideration3" : "t-shirts",
		"consideration4" : "jeans",
		"consideration5" : "sneakers",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 14527.204999991227,
		"rt_considerations" : 42895.14999999665,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "wendys",
		"consideration2" : "subway",
		"consideration3" : "burger king",
		"consideration4" : "panerra",
		"consideration5" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3QNCW3LR2AVOV",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 13630.284999992,
		"rt_considerations" : 28635.040000022855,
		"age" : 52,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "ucu6bdtxcg80",
		"consideration1" : "Bed ",
		"consideration2" : "End table",
		"consideration3" : "Love seat",
		"consideration4" : "Couch",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "n.a"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "cow",
		"rt_response" : 60504.500000039116,
		"rt_considerations" : 57891.99500007089,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "bird",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "tiger",
		"consideration5" : "whale",
		"consideration6" : "shark",
		"consideration7" : "horse",
		"consideration8" : "goat"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Mango",
		"rt_response" : 15373.060000012629,
		"rt_considerations" : 90043.22999995202,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "banana",
		"consideration3" : "mango",
		"consideration4" : "strawberry",
		"consideration5" : "buleberry",
		"consideration6" : "eggs",
		"consideration7" : "orange",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Saint Patricks Day",
		"rt_response" : 44592.46499999426,
		"rt_considerations" : 58612.18499997631,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "Easter",
		"consideration2" : "4th of july",
		"consideration3" : "Thansgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Christmas",
		"consideration5" : "Halloween",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 35062.27500003297,
		"rt_considerations" : 80410.15500004869,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "bed",
		"consideration4" : "dresser",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 15216.235000058077,
		"rt_considerations" : 96991.8099999195,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "garbage disposal",
		"consideration3" : "microwave",
		"consideration4" : "blender",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 21634.63500002399,
		"rt_considerations" : 71414.86000001896,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "Chilis",
		"consideration2" : "TGI Fridays",
		"consideration3" : "Lone Star",
		"consideration4" : "Applebees",
		"consideration5" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration6" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration7" : "KFC",
		"consideration8" : "Wendys"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Golf",
		"rt_response" : 6081.679999944754,
		"rt_considerations" : 72665.68500001449,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "golf",
		"consideration5" : "tennis",
		"consideration6" : "basketball",
		"consideration7" : "wrestling",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 16147.359999944456,
		"rt_considerations" : 46774.57000000868,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "shirts",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "coat",
		"consideration5" : "hat",
		"consideration6" : "shoes",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Cashier",
		"rt_response" : 53939.09999995958,
		"rt_considerations" : 90851.73999995459,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "driver",
		"consideration2" : "construction",
		"consideration3" : "cashier",
		"consideration4" : "secretary",
		"consideration5" : "waiter",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2VLREMQN7N1N6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Peppers",
		"rt_response" : 33983.864999958314,
		"rt_considerations" : 72541.12000006717,
		"age" : 51,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "uhuvwld8h1f6",
		"consideration1" : "carrots",
		"consideration2" : "onions",
		"consideration3" : "potato",
		"consideration4" : "lettuce",
		"consideration5" : "tomato",
		"consideration6" : "celery",
		"consideration7" : "peppers",
		"consideration8" : "squash"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 30663.799999980256,
		"rt_considerations" : 77682.20999999903,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Cereal",
		"consideration2" : "PancakeWaffles",
		"consideration3" : "Toast",
		"consideration4" : "Eggs",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Manufacturing",
		"rt_response" : 65016.61500002956,
		"rt_considerations" : 53065.80500002019,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Manufacturing",
		"consideration2" : "Construction",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 6734.639999980573,
		"rt_considerations" : 47273.65500002634,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Rugby",
		"consideration3" : "Soccer",
		"consideration4" : "Basketball",
		"consideration5" : "Baseball",
		"consideration6" : "Hockey",
		"consideration7" : "Lacross",
		"consideration8" : "Weight lifting"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "T-Shirt",
		"rt_response" : 8290.625000023283,
		"rt_considerations" : 35678.23999997927,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Pants",
		"consideration2" : "Shorts",
		"consideration3" : "Tank Tops",
		"consideration4" : "Bikinis",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Duck",
		"rt_response" : 31445.41000004392,
		"rt_considerations" : 64175.71500001941,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "panda",
		"consideration2" : "Camel",
		"consideration3" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration4" : "Elephant",
		"consideration5" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration6" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 8336.605000018608,
		"rt_considerations" : 27763.245000038296,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "Oven",
		"consideration3" : "Sink",
		"consideration4" : "Stove",
		"consideration5" : "Microwave",
		"consideration6" : "Toaster",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Chair",
		"rt_response" : 7554.285000020172,
		"rt_considerations" : 30002.335000026505,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Sofa",
		"consideration3" : "Table",
		"consideration4" : "Bookcase",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Burger King",
		"rt_response" : 6801.68000003323,
		"rt_considerations" : 48306.09500000719,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "Carls Jr (Hardees)",
		"consideration3" : "Papa Johns",
		"consideration4" : "Pizza Hut",
		"consideration5" : "Popeyes",
		"consideration6" : "Chick-Fil-A",
		"consideration7" : "Mc Donalds",
		"consideration8" : "Subway"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 11884.529999981169,
		"rt_considerations" : 39988.125000032596,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Birthday",
		"consideration4" : "New Years",
		"consideration5" : "Columbus Day",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2N4DD7IS7EI2D",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Green Onions",
		"rt_response" : 9465.175000019372,
		"rt_considerations" : 34035.71500000544,
		"age" : 30,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "s9wdq120q8e3",
		"consideration1" : "Tomatos",
		"consideration2" : "Onions",
		"consideration3" : "Lettuce",
		"consideration4" : "Cabbage",
		"consideration5" : "Spinach ",
		"consideration6" : "Carrots",
		"consideration7" : "Peas",
		"consideration8" : "Corn"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years Eve",
		"rt_response" : 8241,
		"rt_considerations" : 20165,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "prostitute",
		"rt_response" : 4969,
		"rt_considerations" : 8612,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "prostitute",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "tea tray",
		"rt_response" : 17319,
		"rt_considerations" : 14389,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "end table",
		"consideration2" : "card table",
		"consideration3" : "tea tray",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "baseball",
		"rt_response" : 20459,
		"rt_considerations" : 18332,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pumpkin pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 24387,
		"rt_considerations" : 10605,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "peppers",
		"rt_response" : 12810,
		"rt_considerations" : 11598,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "peppers",
		"consideration2" : "carrots",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "grizzly bear",
		"rt_response" : 7540,
		"rt_considerations" : 16105,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "grizzly bear",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "zebra",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "t-shirt",
		"rt_response" : 7607,
		"rt_considerations" : 8831,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "t-shirt",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Red Lobster",
		"rt_response" : 11146,
		"rt_considerations" : 9855,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "Red Lobster",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2TDK0LD62WZ8Y",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 21403,
		"rt_considerations" : 13475,
		"age" : 62,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "atf29m0hqeg8",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 30654.609999997774,
		"rt_considerations" : 145505.39000000572,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "bed",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "stool",
		"consideration5" : "lamp",
		"consideration6" : "recliner",
		"consideration7" : "loveseat",
		"consideration8" : "dresser"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "gloves",
		"rt_response" : 24287.779999998747,
		"rt_considerations" : 49644.92500000051,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "underwear",
		"consideration2" : "bras",
		"consideration3" : "socks",
		"consideration4" : "shoes",
		"consideration5" : "shorts",
		"consideration6" : "pants",
		"consideration7" : "shirts",
		"consideration8" : "scarfs"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Golden Corral",
		"rt_response" : 12439.024999999674,
		"rt_considerations" : 66241.75000000105,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Hardees",
		"consideration3" : "Dairy Queen",
		"consideration4" : "Wendys",
		"consideration5" : "Hwy 55",
		"consideration6" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration7" : "Arbys",
		"consideration8" : "Burger King"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "squash",
		"rt_response" : 23960.265000001527,
		"rt_considerations" : 145331.72000000195,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "bell pepper",
		"consideration3" : "lettuce",
		"consideration4" : "beans",
		"consideration5" : "potatos",
		"consideration6" : "coen",
		"consideration7" : "onion",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Motivational Speaker",
		"rt_response" : 17412.925000011455,
		"rt_considerations" : 120983.5599999933,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "lawyer",
		"consideration2" : "preacher",
		"consideration3" : "CEO",
		"consideration4" : "President",
		"consideration5" : "teacher",
		"consideration6" : "engineer",
		"consideration7" : "sales",
		"consideration8" : "chef"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 16925.73000000266,
		"rt_considerations" : 96559.59499999881,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "bacon",
		"consideration2" : "sausage",
		"consideration3" : "biscuit",
		"consideration4" : "eggs",
		"consideration5" : "pancakes",
		"consideration6" : "grits",
		"consideration7" : "hashbrowns",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 11760.720000005676,
		"rt_considerations" : 173075.42999999714,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "bear",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "rhinicerous",
		"consideration5" : "panda",
		"consideration6" : "boa",
		"consideration7" : "seal",
		"consideration8" : "alligator"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 57433.97500000708,
		"rt_considerations" : 155250.5600000003,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "mixer",
		"consideration2" : "toaster",
		"consideration3" : "food processor",
		"consideration4" : "microwave",
		"consideration5" : "waffle iron",
		"consideration6" : "keurig coffee machine",
		"consideration7" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years",
		"rt_response" : 12659.99500000896,
		"rt_considerations" : 61639.7999999898,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "4th of july",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration5" : "Easter",
		"consideration6" : "Halloween",
		"consideration7" : "St. Patricks Day",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AHMHG8491PRQW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "baseball",
		"rt_response" : 8668.460000000894,
		"rt_considerations" : 108015.34499999275,
		"age" : 61,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "07kzeuowbrk8",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "tennis",
		"consideration4" : "polo",
		"consideration5" : "race car driving",
		"consideration6" : "roller skating",
		"consideration7" : "snow sledding",
		"consideration8" : "horse racing"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 8846.460000029765,
		"rt_considerations" : 10374.205000000075,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 473094.23499996774,
		"rt_considerations" : 9277.464999933727,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "gerbil",
		"rt_response" : 20470.710000023246,
		"rt_considerations" : 16653.809999930672,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "gerbil",
		"consideration2" : "mouse",
		"consideration3" : "aardvark",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "cereal",
		"rt_response" : 4165.924999979325,
		"rt_considerations" : 10821.629999903962,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 4775.140000041574,
		"rt_considerations" : 7037.1199999935925,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "couch",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 4950.610000058077,
		"rt_considerations" : 7149.815000011586,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Burger King",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "t-shirts",
		"rt_response" : 3310.490000061691,
		"rt_considerations" : 13493.090000003576,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "t-shirts",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "cashier",
		"rt_response" : 7118.099999963306,
		"rt_considerations" : 11414.209999958985,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "accountant",
		"consideration2" : "cashier",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "grapes",
		"rt_response" : 3022.38999994006,
		"rt_considerations" : 10493.87999996543,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "grapes",
		"consideration2" : "spinach",
		"consideration3" : "orange",
		"consideration4" : "apple",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EXM21XS6NZV5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "thanksgiving",
		"rt_response" : 5573.894999921322,
		"rt_considerations" : 8718.349999981001,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "caws4bpqh4vt",
		"consideration1" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "christmas",
		"consideration3" : "halloween",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Green",
		"rt_response" : 12997.700000065379,
		"rt_considerations" : 71730.29999993742,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Green",
		"consideration2" : "Red",
		"consideration3" : "Brown",
		"consideration4" : "Orange",
		"consideration5" : "Purple",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Basketball",
		"rt_response" : 11755.400000023656,
		"rt_considerations" : 28500.49999996554,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Basketball",
		"consideration2" : "Soccer",
		"consideration3" : "Football",
		"consideration4" : "Volleyball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "T-shirts",
		"rt_response" : 7908.3999999566,
		"rt_considerations" : 30333.600000012666,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "T-shirts",
		"consideration2" : "Jeans",
		"consideration3" : "Underwear",
		"consideration4" : "Sweaters",
		"consideration5" : "Belts",
		"consideration6" : "Sunglasses",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Memorial day",
		"rt_response" : 107604.80000008829,
		"rt_considerations" : 38406.69999993406,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Memorial day",
		"consideration2" : "MLK day",
		"consideration3" : "Veterans day",
		"consideration4" : "4th of July",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 385179.69999997877,
		"rt_considerations" : 193496.89999991097,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "batter mixer",
		"consideration2" : "blender",
		"consideration3" : "grill",
		"consideration4" : "oven",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Teacher",
		"rt_response" : 19498.20000003092,
		"rt_considerations" : 69862.80000000261,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Engineer",
		"consideration2" : "Teacher",
		"consideration3" : "Professor ",
		"consideration4" : "Accountant",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Chair",
		"rt_response" : 10673.700000043027,
		"rt_considerations" : 47724.000000045635,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Couch",
		"consideration3" : "Sofa",
		"consideration4" : "Bed",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Turkey patties",
		"rt_response" : 66798.59999998007,
		"rt_considerations" : 83571.80000003427,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Turkey Patties and sausages",
		"consideration2" : "Chicken patties and sausages",
		"consideration3" : "Omelette with portobello mushrooms",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 5702.700000023469,
		"rt_considerations" : 34717.30000001844,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Bear",
		"consideration4" : "Elephant",
		"consideration5" : "Donkey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3G5OWGKHW6OL5",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Jack in the box",
		"rt_response" : 8027.199999894947,
		"rt_considerations" : 29276.00000007078,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "Salvadorian",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "bdejl0d8dw71",
		"consideration1" : "Jack in the box",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 33477.95000000042,
		"rt_considerations" : 63923.20999999356,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Electric kettle",
		"consideration2" : "Oven",
		"consideration3" : "blender",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Electrician",
		"rt_response" : 28081.144999989192,
		"rt_considerations" : 49825.5050000007,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Plumber",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 24231.079999997746,
		"rt_considerations" : 27172.0900000073,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Easter",
		"consideration2" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Omelette",
		"rt_response" : 7075.6600000022445,
		"rt_considerations" : 45981.65999999037,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "cereal",
		"consideration2" : "Pop tart",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Tennis",
		"rt_response" : 15012.744999999995,
		"rt_considerations" : 31069.740000006277,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Soccer",
		"consideration2" : "Cricket",
		"consideration3" : "Field hockey",
		"consideration4" : "Baseball",
		"consideration5" : "Rugby",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 11692.689999996219,
		"rt_considerations" : 28111.49999999907,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Jacket",
		"consideration2" : "Hat",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Stool",
		"rt_response" : 19595.060000006924,
		"rt_considerations" : 39477.429999999,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Squash",
		"rt_response" : 29415.059999999357,
		"rt_considerations" : 34385.745000006864,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "Eggplant",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Gorilla",
		"rt_response" : 10064.5050000021,
		"rt_considerations" : 20867.484999995213,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Lion",
		"consideration3" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A7O82NXM2PI12",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Checkers",
		"rt_response" : 18583.21500000602,
		"rt_considerations" : 45457.51500000188,
		"age" : 40,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "8dwkkumhs8q3",
		"consideration1" : "Jack-in-the--Box",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "farmer",
		"rt_response" : 8544,
		"rt_considerations" : 104448,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "laborer",
		"consideration2" : "builder",
		"consideration3" : "inventor",
		"consideration4" : "farmer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "sweater",
		"rt_response" : 8592,
		"rt_considerations" : 27543,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "shoes",
		"consideration2" : "t shirt",
		"consideration3" : "hat",
		"consideration4" : "sweater",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Burger King",
		"rt_response" : 12413,
		"rt_considerations" : 19143,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Chipolte",
		"consideration4" : "Burger King",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 7258,
		"rt_considerations" : 10204,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "microwave",
		"rt_response" : 12746,
		"rt_considerations" : 22144,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "toaster",
		"consideration4" : "blender",
		"consideration5" : "fridge",
		"consideration6" : "microwave",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 9097,
		"rt_considerations" : 13398,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "sausage",
		"consideration2" : "bacon",
		"consideration3" : "hasbrowns",
		"consideration4" : "eggs",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 28347,
		"rt_considerations" : 29517,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "mattress",
		"consideration2" : "coffee table",
		"consideration3" : "couch",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 9794,
		"rt_considerations" : 27855,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "zebra",
		"consideration4" : "antelope",
		"consideration5" : "bird",
		"consideration6" : "monkey",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Easter",
		"rt_response" : 5331,
		"rt_considerations" : 13323,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "valentines day",
		"consideration2" : "easter",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2EMTSJS47K8SU",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "spinach",
		"rt_response" : 9330,
		"rt_considerations" : 27114,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "upsm9hld62sv",
		"consideration1" : "celery",
		"consideration2" : "broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration4" : "zucchini",
		"consideration5" : "avocado",
		"consideration6" : "spinach",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Shoes",
		"rt_response" : 4342.8449999773875,
		"rt_considerations" : 95113.26999997254,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Nike Air Max",
		"consideration2" : "Air Jordans",
		"consideration3" : "Adidas Slides",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Presidents Day",
		"rt_response" : 13255.865000071935,
		"rt_considerations" : 84823.39499995578,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Ash Wednesday",
		"consideration2" : "Presidents Day",
		"consideration3" : "Good Friday",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Farmer",
		"rt_response" : 13176.070000045002,
		"rt_considerations" : 25758.159999968484,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Farmer",
		"consideration2" : "Miner",
		"consideration3" : "Painter",
		"consideration4" : "Servant",
		"consideration5" : "Soldier",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Toaster",
		"rt_response" : 4782.34000003431,
		"rt_considerations" : 43032.87499991711,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Toaster",
		"consideration2" : "Blender",
		"consideration3" : "Wisk",
		"consideration4" : "Food processor",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 3158.3050000481308,
		"rt_considerations" : 26022.465000045486,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Couch",
		"consideration2" : "Television",
		"consideration3" : "Table",
		"consideration4" : "Rug",
		"consideration5" : "Stove",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 5094.485000008717,
		"rt_considerations" : 15516.380000044592,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Soccer",
		"consideration4" : "Volleyball",
		"consideration5" : "Cricket",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Dennys",
		"rt_response" : 10735.370000009425,
		"rt_considerations" : 23389.824999962002,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Dennys",
		"consideration2" : "Applebees",
		"consideration3" : "Popeyes",
		"consideration4" : "Burger King",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Potato",
		"rt_response" : 5494.8949998943135,
		"rt_considerations" : 29750.38499990478,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Potato",
		"consideration2" : "Tomato",
		"consideration3" : "Spinach",
		"consideration4" : "Carrots",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 6126.384999952279,
		"rt_considerations" : 19852.859999984503,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Lion",
		"consideration2" : "Tiger",
		"consideration3" : "Elephant",
		"consideration4" : "Wolf",
		"consideration5" : "Bobcat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3MGDMVIQ1ZZ5S",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 5870.475000003353,
		"rt_considerations" : 25110.169999999925,
		"age" : 22,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "7tlurm8j1cgv",
		"consideration1" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "Waffles",
		"consideration3" : "Burrito",
		"consideration4" : "Hash browns",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Pilots.",
		"rt_response" : 20592.41999999722,
		"rt_considerations" : 130453.32000000053,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "lifeguard",
		"consideration2" : "police officer",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "egg yolk",
		"rt_response" : 31851.08500000206,
		"rt_considerations" : 17122.364999999263,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "blueberries",
		"consideration2" : "mango",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 9739.78999999963,
		"rt_considerations" : 13625.879999999597,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "shirts",
		"consideration2" : "jeans",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "brussels sprouts",
		"rt_response" : 21930.355000000418,
		"rt_considerations" : 18976.20999999711,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "turnips",
		"consideration2" : "beets",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "food processor",
		"rt_response" : 12818.615000000107,
		"rt_considerations" : 13242.355000002135,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "a bed",
		"rt_response" : 8474.43999999814,
		"rt_considerations" : 12657.940000000992,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "loveseat",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "track",
		"rt_response" : 13616.59999999759,
		"rt_considerations" : 13114.420000001672,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "a tiger",
		"rt_response" : 12212.88000000274,
		"rt_considerations" : 11352.404999997816,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "bear",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Panera",
		"rt_response" : 19104.569999999483,
		"rt_considerations" : 11803.955000003101,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "Chipotle",
		"consideration2" : "Moes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2ZDEERVRN5AMC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Independence Day",
		"rt_response" : 38923.885000000184,
		"rt_considerations" : 20657.31500000035,
		"age" : 29,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "1q4mdvxdl8ou",
		"consideration1" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "doctor",
		"rt_response" : 7611.525000000256,
		"rt_considerations" : 17726.11500000037,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "lawyer",
		"consideration2" : "teacher",
		"consideration3" : "coach",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 7117.119999999879,
		"rt_considerations" : 16872.940000000177,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 3394.5950000006706,
		"rt_considerations" : 19691.495000000024,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "oatmeal",
		"rt_response" : 5438.89499999932,
		"rt_considerations" : 15033.360000000364,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 12230.810000000027,
		"rt_considerations" : 17566.635000000126,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 5565.880000000121,
		"rt_considerations" : 12671.739999999758,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "zebra",
		"consideration2" : "monkey",
		"consideration3" : "bear",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 6422.944999999367,
		"rt_considerations" : 12993.780000000726,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 4172.414999999979,
		"rt_considerations" : 15465.304999999702,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "coat",
		"consideration2" : "underwear",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Chiptotle",
		"rt_response" : 16805.124999999884,
		"rt_considerations" : 14428.380000000296,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "Applebees",
		"consideration2" : "Chilis",
		"consideration3" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OVX9UW5WANQE",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "stove",
		"rt_response" : 4429.75499999919,
		"rt_considerations" : 9933.939999999886,
		"age" : 47,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "hxhvaxmese9n",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Shirt",
		"rt_response" : 10736.680000001797,
		"rt_considerations" : 18690.52499999816,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Pants",
		"consideration2" : "Shirts",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Omelet",
		"rt_response" : 17095.33999999985,
		"rt_considerations" : 29820.37999999011,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "Waffles",
		"consideration3" : "Eggs",
		"consideration4" : "Omelet",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Taco Bell",
		"rt_response" : 23867.350000000442,
		"rt_considerations" : 24484.909999999218,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "Mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Coat Rack",
		"rt_response" : 19281.695000012405,
		"rt_considerations" : 21062.455000006594,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Table",
		"consideration2" : "Chair",
		"consideration3" : "Coat Rack",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Basket Ball",
		"rt_response" : 15277.7700000006,
		"rt_considerations" : 19148.560000001453,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Wrestling",
		"consideration2" : "Basket Ball",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Avacado",
		"rt_response" : 14829.555000003893,
		"rt_considerations" : 34560.73499999184,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Tomato",
		"consideration2" : "Spinach",
		"consideration3" : "Avocado",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Trash Compactor",
		"rt_response" : 11567.460000005667,
		"rt_considerations" : 24028.344999998808,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Dish Washer",
		"consideration2" : "Trash Compactor",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "hippopotamus",
		"rt_response" : 36413.36500000034,
		"rt_considerations" : 26831.01500000339,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Ostrich ",
		"consideration2" : "Alligator",
		"consideration3" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the most forgettable?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Veterans Day",
		"rt_response" : 16197.644999992917,
		"rt_considerations" : 31162.53499999584,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration2" : "Veterans Day",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1F5E941TP0UIZ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Prostitute  ",
		"rt_response" : 12779.770000008284,
		"rt_considerations" : 19746.70000000333,
		"age" : 49,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "d8s11tafmmjm",
		"consideration1" : "Prostitute  ",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potatoes",
		"rt_response" : 22382.82000005711,
		"rt_considerations" : 46546.68000002857,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration2" : "broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "asparagus",
		"consideration4" : "carrots",
		"consideration5" : "onions",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Halloween",
		"rt_response" : 15701.505000004545,
		"rt_considerations" : 71738.69500006549,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "4th of July",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Bra",
		"rt_response" : 7472.339999978431,
		"rt_considerations" : 33681.05000001378,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "hats",
		"consideration2" : "socks",
		"consideration3" : "underwear",
		"consideration4" : "belt",
		"consideration5" : "scarf",
		"consideration6" : "gloves",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Golden Coral",
		"rt_response" : 12819.155000033788,
		"rt_considerations" : 67536.41000005882,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "Burger Kind",
		"consideration2" : "Chipolte",
		"consideration3" : "Subway",
		"consideration4" : "Mcdonalds",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Gymnastics",
		"rt_response" : 9382.330000051297,
		"rt_considerations" : 24874.605000019073,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "Hockey",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "baseball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Panda",
		"rt_response" : 14002.184999990277,
		"rt_considerations" : 24222.375000012107,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "Fish",
		"consideration2" : "Monkey",
		"consideration3" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "Lion",
		"consideration5" : "Rhinoceros",
		"consideration6" : "Cheetah",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Cereal",
		"rt_response" : 6882.734999991953,
		"rt_considerations" : 28921.879999921657,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "Apples",
		"consideration2" : "Grapes",
		"consideration3" : "Oranges",
		"consideration4" : "Hash",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 8813.87499999255,
		"rt_considerations" : 29351.024999981746,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "can opener",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "fridge",
		"consideration4" : "oven",
		"consideration5" : "stove",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Server",
		"rt_response" : 5924.155000015162,
		"rt_considerations" : 27704.655000008643,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "Cook",
		"consideration2" : "maid",
		"consideration3" : "Labourer",
		"consideration4" : "cashier",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A34TRV5A6W5QB2",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Vanity",
		"rt_response" : 33345.444999984466,
		"rt_considerations" : 25874.285000027157,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "yjgfv7vltozo",
		"consideration1" : "dresser",
		"consideration2" : "coffee table",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs with salsa",
		"rt_response" : 19683.52999999979,
		"rt_considerations" : 53204.185000000056,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "burrito",
		"consideration4" : "eggs with salsa",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "easter",
		"rt_response" : 34152.96999999965,
		"rt_considerations" : 42444.074999999895,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "halloween",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "valentines day",
		"consideration4" : "easter",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 7104.83000000022,
		"rt_considerations" : 33983.13000000009,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "monkey",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "dennys",
		"rt_response" : 7238.859999999928,
		"rt_considerations" : 27578.215000000026,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "dennys",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teacher",
		"rt_response" : 10731.644999999844,
		"rt_considerations" : 31388.385000000242,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "garbage truck driver",
		"consideration2" : "teacher",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 7021.209999999846,
		"rt_considerations" : 22965.83999999985,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "hockey",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "cheese grater",
		"rt_response" : 30930.494999999646,
		"rt_considerations" : 26595.695000000007,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "cheese grater",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "sweatshirt",
		"rt_response" : 7809.449999999721,
		"rt_considerations" : 19733.64999999921,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "sweatshirt",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pumpkin",
		"rt_response" : 7336.31000000058,
		"rt_considerations" : 20343.669999999285,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A5XB2OFILUVP9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "candle stick",
		"rt_response" : 13367.3549999994,
		"rt_considerations" : 47875.494999999355,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "s6ec6z7khdul",
		"consideration1" : "table",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "candlestick (holder)",
		"consideration4" : "candlestick",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 22814.325000043027,
		"rt_considerations" : 63204.64500004891,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "blender",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "stove",
		"consideration4" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration5" : "toaster oven",
		"consideration6" : "slow cooker",
		"consideration7" : "air fryer",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "bed",
		"rt_response" : 53166.889999993145,
		"rt_considerations" : 46253.08000005316,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "dresser",
		"consideration3" : "chest of drawers",
		"consideration4" : "easy chair",
		"consideration5" : "recliner",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "fighter pilot",
		"rt_response" : 16725.40500003379,
		"rt_considerations" : 97970.38499999326,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "data entry clerk",
		"consideration2" : "hunting guide",
		"consideration3" : "wildlife tracker",
		"consideration4" : "medical research scientist",
		"consideration5" : "professional gamer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "peacock",
		"rt_response" : 24331.400000024587,
		"rt_considerations" : 78841.47500002291,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "monkey",
		"consideration2" : "seal",
		"consideration3" : "snake",
		"consideration4" : "giraffe",
		"consideration5" : "bird",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years Eve",
		"rt_response" : 9829.050000058487,
		"rt_considerations" : 71789.17500004172,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "St. Patricks Day",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "July 4",
		"consideration4" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration5" : "Memorial Day",
		"consideration6" : "Cinco de Mayo",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bagel",
		"rt_response" : 15599.33999995701,
		"rt_considerations" : 108840.9700000193,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "hot cereal",
		"consideration2" : "sausage patties",
		"consideration3" : "fruit bowl",
		"consideration4" : "steak and eggs",
		"consideration5" : "burrito",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "skydiving",
		"rt_response" : 14553.019999992102,
		"rt_considerations" : 94582.57500000764,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "hockey",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "La Crosse",
		"consideration4" : "ski jumping",
		"consideration5" : "paint ball battles",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Texas Roadhouse",
		"rt_response" : 31617.42000002414,
		"rt_considerations" : 95810.62500004191,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Arbys",
		"consideration3" : "IHOP",
		"consideration4" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration5" : "Del Taco",
		"consideration6" : "Lottaburger",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "onions",
		"rt_response" : 15890.745000098832,
		"rt_considerations" : 62224.75499997381,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "potatoes",
		"consideration2" : "cabbage",
		"consideration3" : "beets",
		"consideration4" : "turnips",
		"consideration5" : "beans",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1T429RLLFTG35",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "mens briefs",
		"rt_response" : 11060.990000027232,
		"rt_considerations" : 89696.69500004966,
		"age" : 78,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "2vdq28qdsnnk",
		"consideration1" : "mens underwear T-shirts",
		"consideration2" : "raincoats",
		"consideration3" : "ponchos",
		"consideration4" : "rain boots",
		"consideration5" : "coveralls",
		"consideration6" : "painters uniforms",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "nursing",
		"rt_response" : 11440.214999951422,
		"rt_considerations" : 77411.2750000204,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "police officer",
		"consideration2" : "teacher",
		"consideration3" : "fast food worker",
		"consideration4" : "first job",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pepper",
		"rt_response" : 11747.574999986682,
		"rt_considerations" : 25259.64499998372,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "potato",
		"consideration3" : "carrot",
		"consideration4" : "pepper",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "HASHBROWNS",
		"rt_response" : 17475.72000004584,
		"rt_considerations" : 33202.62499997625,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "EGGS",
		"consideration2" : "PANCAKES",
		"consideration3" : "CEREAL",
		"consideration4" : "WAFFLES",
		"consideration5" : "HASHBROWNS OR POTATOES",
		"consideration6" : "POPTARTS",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "CHAIR",
		"rt_response" : 10372.929999954067,
		"rt_considerations" : 10683.429999975488,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "CHAIR LEG",
		"consideration2" : "CHAIR",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA ",
		"consideration7" : "NA ",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "TENNIS",
		"rt_response" : 5320.805000024848,
		"rt_considerations" : 18540.225000004284,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "BASKETBAL",
		"consideration2" : "SWIMMNG",
		"consideration3" : "TENNIS",
		"consideration4" : "NA ",
		"consideration5" : "NA ",
		"consideration6" : "NA ",
		"consideration7" : "NA ",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "crockpot",
		"rt_response" : 27857.16999997385,
		"rt_considerations" : 15381.125000014435,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "blender ",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na ",
		"consideration5" : "na na ",
		"consideration6" : "na ",
		"consideration7" : "na ",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "cheesecake factory",
		"rt_response" : 22076.379999984056,
		"rt_considerations" : 15637.950000003912,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "ryans ",
		"consideration3" : "mcdonalds ",
		"consideration4" : "na ",
		"consideration5" : "na ",
		"consideration6" : "na ",
		"consideration7" : "na ",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "4th of july",
		"rt_response" : 21193.6299999943,
		"rt_considerations" : 12658.634999999776,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "na ",
		"consideration3" : "na ",
		"consideration4" : "na ",
		"consideration5" : "na ",
		"consideration6" : "na ",
		"consideration7" : "na ",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "polar bear",
		"rt_response" : 230834.13500001188,
		"rt_considerations" : 20985.860000015236,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "baboon",
		"consideration2" : "monkey ",
		"consideration3" : "elephant ",
		"consideration4" : "camel ",
		"consideration5" : "na ",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na ",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3OTBMKOEQ410P",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "baby clothes",
		"rt_response" : 11128.710000019055,
		"rt_considerations" : 18410.210000001825,
		"age" : 28,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "hebrew israelite ",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "cd1wsfy0296o",
		"consideration1" : "shirt ",
		"consideration2" : "pants ",
		"consideration3" : "kids clothes",
		"consideration4" : "jackets",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Lion",
		"rt_response" : 11323.975000006612,
		"rt_considerations" : 35522.79499999713,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Jaguar",
		"consideration3" : "Tiger",
		"consideration4" : "Lion",
		"consideration5" : "Monkey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "burrito",
		"rt_response" : 11340.30999999959,
		"rt_considerations" : 15400.605000002543,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Eggs",
		"consideration2" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "Waffles",
		"consideration4" : "Cereal",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Applebees",
		"rt_response" : 8088.29000001424,
		"rt_considerations" : 22501.820000004955,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Chilis",
		"consideration2" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration3" : "Applebees",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Sweet corn",
		"rt_response" : 23944.83500000206,
		"rt_considerations" : 21138.869999995222,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Celery",
		"consideration2" : "Broccoli",
		"consideration3" : "Peas",
		"consideration4" : "Sweet corn",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 10954.364999983227,
		"rt_considerations" : 11723.324999999022,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Couch",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Track",
		"rt_response" : 12589.719999989029,
		"rt_considerations" : 18451.015000027837,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Basketball",
		"consideration2" : "Baseball",
		"consideration3" : "Soccer",
		"consideration4" : "Track",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Cashier",
		"rt_response" : 6225.5350000050385,
		"rt_considerations" : 19670.30500000692,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Waiter",
		"consideration2" : "Sales",
		"consideration3" : "Cashier",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 5866.5449999971315,
		"rt_considerations" : 13260.429999994813,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Halloween",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "Christmas",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Oven",
		"rt_response" : 6840.689999982715,
		"rt_considerations" : 12003.854999988107,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Stove",
		"consideration2" : "Microwave",
		"consideration3" : "Oven",
		"consideration4" : "Refrigerator",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1HMO9XPRPUPWJ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Jeans",
		"rt_response" : 12023.214999993797,
		"rt_considerations" : 13618.144999985816,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "x4bpf6xg2bk8",
		"consideration1" : "Underwear",
		"consideration2" : "Shoes",
		"consideration3" : "Shirts",
		"consideration4" : "Blouse",
		"consideration5" : "Jeans",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "refrigerator",
		"rt_response" : 19131.50500000029,
		"rt_considerations" : 44958.96499999981,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration2" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration3" : "garbage disposal",
		"consideration4" : "slow cooker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "basketball",
		"rt_response" : 11266.174999999756,
		"rt_considerations" : 19688.444999999774,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "football",
		"consideration5" : "hockey",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "five guys",
		"rt_response" : 34576.59999999941,
		"rt_considerations" : 26530.015000000276,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "five guys",
		"consideration2" : "popeyes",
		"consideration3" : "longhorns",
		"consideration4" : "applebees",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 19151.689999999682,
		"rt_considerations" : 76422.84500000009,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "gorilla",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "giraffe",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 9973.520000000426,
		"rt_considerations" : 17671.820000000473,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "halloween",
		"consideration3" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "easter",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 8198.354999999516,
		"rt_considerations" : 47592.00499999948,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "sofa",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "lamp",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "head coach",
		"rt_response" : 13496.624999999767,
		"rt_considerations" : 27973.32999999984,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "head coach",
		"consideration2" : "announcer",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "911 operator",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "waffles",
		"rt_response" : 13113.185000000172,
		"rt_considerations" : 29974.804999999877,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "waffles",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "biscuits and gravy",
		"consideration4" : "eggs",
		"consideration5" : "oatmeal",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "corn",
		"rt_response" : 11130.930000000226,
		"rt_considerations" : 17414.21999999968,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "tomatoes",
		"consideration3" : "peppers",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A6BXO4JNQP7W9",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 5217.545000000449,
		"rt_considerations" : 15667.17499999958,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "53yl9kdr0vvl",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "hat",
		"consideration4" : "socks",
		"consideration5" : "underwear",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pumpkin",
		"rt_response" : 10539.915000001201,
		"rt_considerations" : 34542.560000001686,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "potato",
		"consideration3" : "lettuce",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "n.a"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "waffle house",
		"rt_response" : 11202.684999996563,
		"rt_considerations" : 31001.175000012154,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "checkers",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "burger king",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "st patricks day",
		"rt_response" : 13790.760000003502,
		"rt_considerations" : 30885.680000006687,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "4th of july",
		"consideration2" : "veterans day",
		"consideration3" : "memorial day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "pilot",
		"rt_response" : 5020.890000014333,
		"rt_considerations" : 28987.120000005234,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "sniper",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "stool",
		"rt_response" : 20777.13999999105,
		"rt_considerations" : 13873.615000018617,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "tie",
		"rt_response" : 10407.205000024987,
		"rt_considerations" : 14442.070000019157,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "belt",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 13224.480000004405,
		"rt_considerations" : 13052.644999988843,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "soccer",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 5613.959999987856,
		"rt_considerations" : 14629.769999999553,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "fridge",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "snake",
		"rt_response" : 15705.600000015693,
		"rt_considerations" : 20306.494999997085,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "bear",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "tiger",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2XQ3P6M9NZNYB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 12056.454999983544,
		"rt_considerations" : 12389.774999988731,
		"age" : 32,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "american",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "nj2qk8mwsjnm",
		"consideration1" : "waffle",
		"consideration2" : "toast",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "lettuce",
		"rt_response" : 87340.43999999994,
		"rt_considerations" : 209532.17499999664,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "Are you kidding me? Broccoli",
		"consideration2" : "cauliflower",
		"consideration3" : "onion",
		"consideration4" : "potato",
		"consideration5" : "pepper",
		"consideration6" : "dill",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 29018.935000000056,
		"rt_considerations" : 126131.86999999743,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "cheeseburger",
		"consideration2" : "hamburger",
		"consideration3" : "fries",
		"consideration4" : "hotdog",
		"consideration5" : "corndog",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 32008.714999999967,
		"rt_considerations" : 134788.51000000216,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration4" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shirt",
		"rt_response" : 10237.58000000089,
		"rt_considerations" : 91053.52000000142,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "socks",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "shirt",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport is easiest to learn?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 19616.480000000563,
		"rt_considerations" : 35552.08499999938,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "foot",
		"consideration2" : "balls",
		"consideration3" : "leg",
		"consideration4" : "arm",
		"consideration5" : "strength",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Omelette",
		"rt_response" : 37287.22500000009,
		"rt_considerations" : 47686.35999999975,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "peppers",
		"consideration3" : "spinach",
		"consideration4" : "potato",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "desk",
		"rt_response" : 12139.905000000028,
		"rt_considerations" : 65450.62500000128,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "working here",
		"consideration2" : "my job",
		"consideration3" : "what i do",
		"consideration4" : "why am i even living here",
		"consideration5" : "why do you keep asking these questions",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "YOU FUCK SHIT, WHY ASK SO MANY QUESTIONS",
		"rt_response" : 81099.4150000005,
		"rt_considerations" : 51376.19999999879,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration2" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration3" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration4" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration5" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration6" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration7" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration8" : "FUCK YOU"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "FUCK YOU",
		"rt_response" : 8935.174999998882,
		"rt_considerations" : 32541.00499999919,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration2" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration3" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration4" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration5" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration6" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration7" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration8" : "FUCK YOU"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : " A3APKUC67F9IMW",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "FUCK YOU",
		"rt_response" : 7181.9749999996275,
		"rt_considerations" : 25289.215000000782,
		"age" : 34,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "58hx6g179j60",
		"consideration1" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration2" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration3" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration4" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration5" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration6" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration7" : "FUCK YOU",
		"consideration8" : "FUCK YOU"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St Patricks Day",
		"rt_response" : 21109.339999995427,
		"rt_considerations" : 36365.55999999109,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "Halloween",
		"consideration3" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration4" : "Valentines Day",
		"consideration5" : "Mardi Gras",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "doctor",
		"rt_response" : 13733.065000007628,
		"rt_considerations" : 48845.18499999831,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "IT",
		"consideration2" : "musician",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "chef",
		"consideration5" : "waiter",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 84370.85000000661,
		"rt_considerations" : 37521.6550000041,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "table",
		"consideration2" : "sofa",
		"consideration3" : "bed",
		"consideration4" : "desk",
		"consideration5" : "nightstand",
		"consideration6" : "dresser",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "duck",
		"rt_response" : 18258.895000006305,
		"rt_considerations" : 32489.31000000448,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "gorilla",
		"consideration4" : "kangaroo",
		"consideration5" : "panda",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is eaten the least in spring?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Squash",
		"rt_response" : 18679.375000006985,
		"rt_considerations" : 60551.955000002636,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "zuchinni",
		"consideration4" : "onion",
		"consideration5" : "broccoli",
		"consideration6" : "corn",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "tie",
		"rt_response" : 14177.129999996396,
		"rt_considerations" : 28017.659999997704,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "jeans",
		"consideration3" : "scarf",
		"consideration4" : "shirt",
		"consideration5" : "dress",
		"consideration6" : "skirt",
		"consideration7" : "hat",
		"consideration8" : "shoes"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most gear?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 13981.4100000076,
		"rt_considerations" : 31835.250000003725,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "golf",
		"consideration3" : "baseball",
		"consideration4" : "rugby",
		"consideration5" : "polo",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "sausage",
		"rt_response" : 67115.09500000102,
		"rt_considerations" : 55741.64500000188,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "sausage",
		"consideration4" : "hashbrowns",
		"consideration5" : "tomato",
		"consideration6" : "steak",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "toaster",
		"rt_response" : 12755.14999999723,
		"rt_considerations" : 20685.8099999954,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "fridge",
		"consideration4" : "oven",
		"consideration5" : "stove",
		"consideration6" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration7" : "mixer",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2B0FLA55RH047",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 15689.279999991413,
		"rt_considerations" : 35663.45499998715,
		"age" : 31,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "Untied States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "qhcf10oz1lze",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Red Lobster",
		"consideration4" : "Olive Garden",
		"consideration5" : "Burger King",
		"consideration6" : "IHOP",
		"consideration7" : "Dennys",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "socks",
		"rt_response" : 10813.355000005686,
		"rt_considerations" : 62570.690000007744,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "socks",
		"consideration2" : "underwear",
		"consideration3" : "belt",
		"consideration4" : "shirt",
		"consideration5" : "pants",
		"consideration6" : "shoes",
		"consideration7" : "trenchcoat",
		"consideration8" : "hat"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "bookcase",
		"rt_response" : 36253.6950000067,
		"rt_considerations" : 91422.23999999987,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "end table",
		"consideration4" : "sofa",
		"consideration5" : "tv stand",
		"consideration6" : "coat rack",
		"consideration7" : "chaise lounge",
		"consideration8" : "foot stool"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "football",
		"rt_response" : 13082.060000000638,
		"rt_considerations" : 121057.55499999213,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "soccer",
		"consideration3" : "basketball",
		"consideration4" : "water polo",
		"consideration5" : "hockey",
		"consideration6" : "field hockey",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 20475.410000013653,
		"rt_considerations" : 60601.2550000014,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "refridgerator",
		"consideration3" : "freezer",
		"consideration4" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration5" : "can opener",
		"consideration6" : "toaster",
		"consideration7" : "microwave",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "polar bear",
		"rt_response" : 19382.55000000936,
		"rt_considerations" : 58404.82000001066,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "polar bear",
		"consideration2" : "bear",
		"consideration3" : "ostrich",
		"consideration4" : "snake",
		"consideration5" : "giraffe",
		"consideration6" : "ox",
		"consideration7" : "buffalo",
		"consideration8" : "cheetah"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most colorful?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "mexican omellet",
		"rt_response" : 20067.955000005895,
		"rt_considerations" : 79769.54999999725,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "mexican omellet",
		"consideration2" : "scrambled eggs",
		"consideration3" : "pancakes",
		"consideration4" : "waffle",
		"consideration5" : "kix cereal",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 13438.134999989416,
		"rt_considerations" : 44528.22500000184,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "burger king",
		"consideration3" : "wendys",
		"consideration4" : "taco bell",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrot",
		"rt_response" : 10190.025000003516,
		"rt_considerations" : 41185.075000001234,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "corn",
		"consideration4" : "beans",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "teaching",
		"rt_response" : 11100.270000009914,
		"rt_considerations" : 51795.289999994566,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "teaching",
		"consideration2" : "broadcaster",
		"consideration3" : "minister",
		"consideration4" : "announcer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A1JM5XNB4NCZR6",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "new years",
		"rt_response" : 11102.525000009337,
		"rt_considerations" : 62130.80999998783,
		"age" : 66,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "usa",
		"nationality" : "usa",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "e6dft9hxx8f6",
		"consideration1" : "new years",
		"consideration2" : "new years eve",
		"consideration3" : "4th of july",
		"consideration4" : "anniversary",
		"consideration5" : "labor day",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "onion",
		"rt_response" : 17785.845000005793,
		"rt_considerations" : 24666.625000012573,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "corn",
		"consideration2" : "apple",
		"consideration3" : "onion",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "scientist",
		"rt_response" : 15283.095000020694,
		"rt_considerations" : 13569.715000048745,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "doctor",
		"consideration2" : "scientist",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "lamp",
		"rt_response" : 76963.99499999825,
		"rt_considerations" : 10104.94499997003,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 10378.144999966025,
		"rt_considerations" : 15783.914999978151,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "taco bell",
		"rt_response" : 20029.099999985192,
		"rt_considerations" : 24164.74500001641,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration3" : "taco bell",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "waffles",
		"rt_response" : 8330.305000010412,
		"rt_considerations" : 15985.375000047497,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "waffles",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 4477.975000045262,
		"rt_considerations" : 9920.490000047721,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "dress",
		"rt_response" : 4850.924999976996,
		"rt_considerations" : 13989.865000010468,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "dress",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 8381.830000027549,
		"rt_considerations" : 14549.645000020973,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "lion",
		"consideration2" : "elephant",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ANLHIS7CZAZVQ",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 40296.0300000268,
		"rt_considerations" : 18127.47499998659,
		"age" : 18,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "white",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "fgy48yh776ly",
		"consideration1" : "hockey",
		"consideration2" : "bowling",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday is the least religious?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Mardi Gras",
		"rt_response" : 22877,
		"rt_considerations" : 87872,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "4th of July",
		"consideration2" : "Haloween",
		"consideration3" : "Easter",
		"consideration4" : "Christmas",
		"consideration5" : "Mardi Gras",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "hockey",
		"rt_response" : 25242,
		"rt_considerations" : 66607,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "polo",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "hockey",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 39614,
		"rt_considerations" : 32185,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "baccon",
		"consideration3" : "toast",
		"consideration4" : "pancacks",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Law Enforcement",
		"rt_response" : 25929,
		"rt_considerations" : 25425,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "Fireman",
		"consideration2" : "Military",
		"consideration3" : "Law Enforcement",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potatoe",
		"rt_response" : 12298,
		"rt_considerations" : 29689,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "carrot",
		"consideration2" : "peas",
		"consideration3" : "potatoe",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is most often purchased online?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "shoes",
		"rt_response" : 15726,
		"rt_considerations" : 22698,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "shoes",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Wendies",
		"rt_response" : 35718,
		"rt_considerations" : 24157,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "Mc Donalds",
		"consideration2" : "Burger King ",
		"consideration3" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration4" : "Wendies",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the biggest feet relative to its body size?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "elephant",
		"rt_response" : 24319,
		"rt_considerations" : 14661,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 7967,
		"rt_considerations" : 19517,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "coffee maker",
		"consideration3" : "blender",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A12XVSIL669PVI",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 11465,
		"rt_considerations" : 14756,
		"age" : 46,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "dwysfz09c94b",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "desk",
		"consideration3" : "sofa",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used the least?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 16644.369999994524,
		"rt_considerations" : 83542.17500000959,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "can opener",
		"consideration3" : "bread maker",
		"consideration4" : "ice maker",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "wrestling",
		"rt_response" : 16487.200000032317,
		"rt_considerations" : 43663.31500001252,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "basketball",
		"consideration2" : "baseball",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture is the most flammable?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 13250.845000031404,
		"rt_considerations" : 25467.23499998916,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "oatmeal",
		"rt_response" : 9611.035000008997,
		"rt_considerations" : 20221.360000025015,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "cold cereal",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "burger king",
		"rt_response" : 14130.165000038687,
		"rt_considerations" : 53840.389999968465,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "mcdonalds",
		"consideration2" : "wendys",
		"consideration3" : "sonic",
		"consideration4" : "arbys",
		"consideration5" : "red lobster",
		"consideration6" : "pizza hut",
		"consideration7" : "dominos",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St Patricks day",
		"rt_response" : 14742.094999994151,
		"rt_considerations" : 32645.635000022594,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "christmas",
		"consideration2" : "thanksgiving ",
		"consideration3" : "independence day",
		"consideration4" : "easter",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrot",
		"rt_response" : 20719.06500001205,
		"rt_considerations" : 19426.434999972116,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "celery",
		"consideration2" : "tomato",
		"consideration3" : "potato",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "polar bear",
		"rt_response" : 29871.189999976195,
		"rt_considerations" : 30373.369999986608,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "giraffe ",
		"consideration2" : "tiger",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "peacock",
		"consideration5" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration6" : "rhinoceros",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is borrowed most frequently?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 6359.9750000284985,
		"rt_considerations" : 21080.435000010766,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "pats",
		"consideration2" : "sweater",
		"consideration3" : "shirt",
		"consideration4" : "gloves",
		"consideration5" : "hat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2AV9XMGPMMMRG",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "optometrist",
		"rt_response" : 11753.120000008494,
		"rt_considerations" : 36855.31000001356,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "jtqpqf9vephf",
		"consideration1" : "police officer",
		"consideration2" : "firefighter",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "doctor",
		"consideration5" : "dentist",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "steak and eggs",
		"rt_response" : 26797,
		"rt_considerations" : 33894,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "waffles",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "quiche",
		"consideration4" : "steak and eggs",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potatoes",
		"rt_response" : 7280,
		"rt_considerations" : 40388,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "corn",
		"consideration3" : "potatoes",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "surgeon",
		"rt_response" : 50613,
		"rt_considerations" : 19510,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "welder",
		"consideration2" : "editor",
		"consideration3" : "teacher",
		"consideration4" : "jewelry repair",
		"consideration5" : "surgeon",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "sofa",
		"rt_response" : 6341,
		"rt_considerations" : 26443,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "table",
		"consideration4" : "chest",
		"consideration5" : "sofa",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 11363,
		"rt_considerations" : 19716,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "pants",
		"consideration4" : "underwear",
		"consideration5" : "coat",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "panda",
		"rt_response" : 105062,
		"rt_considerations" : 28173,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "giraffe",
		"consideration3" : "lion",
		"consideration4" : "flamingo",
		"consideration5" : "panda",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New years eve",
		"rt_response" : 23912,
		"rt_considerations" : 26556,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "St. Patricks Day",
		"consideration3" : "4th of July",
		"consideration4" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "McDonalds",
		"rt_response" : 9481,
		"rt_considerations" : 22643,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration2" : "Wendys",
		"consideration3" : "Burger King",
		"consideration4" : "Jacks",
		"consideration5" : "Sonic",
		"consideration6" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Baseball",
		"rt_response" : 4157,
		"rt_considerations" : 15316,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "tennis",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "hockey",
		"consideration5" : "basketball",
		"consideration6" : "baseball",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3NMQ3019X6YE0",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 13784,
		"rt_considerations" : 15346,
		"age" : 42,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "yt2sxxnrdjqt",
		"consideration1" : "microwave",
		"consideration2" : "oven",
		"consideration3" : "refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "blender",
		"consideration5" : "mixer",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "hippopotamus",
		"rt_response" : 6513.235000078566,
		"rt_considerations" : 32461.415000027046,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "lion",
		"consideration3" : "hippopotamus",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant tends to be the dirtiest?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Texas Roadhouse",
		"rt_response" : 17835.944999940693,
		"rt_considerations" : 17709.24500003457,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "Applebees",
		"consideration2" : "Texas Roadhouse",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "bra",
		"rt_response" : 7199.2450000252575,
		"rt_considerations" : 12958.35500000976,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "pants",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "bra",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 14531.945000053383,
		"rt_considerations" : 13704.144999966957,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "soccer",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable is heaviest for its size?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 5270.450000069104,
		"rt_considerations" : 12723.559999954887,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "potato",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is used most in the winter?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "oven",
		"rt_response" : 6583.244999987073,
		"rt_considerations" : 14221.460000029765,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "oven",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "crockpot",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "farmer",
		"rt_response" : 7319.505000021309,
		"rt_considerations" : 14188.220000010915,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "farmer",
		"consideration2" : "carpenter",
		"consideration3" : "blacksmith",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is worst to eat before working out?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "donuts",
		"rt_response" : 14262.400000006892,
		"rt_considerations" : 15234.705000068061,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "donuts",
		"consideration2" : "pancakes",
		"consideration3" : "eggs",
		"consideration4" : "bacon",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 9810.304999933578,
		"rt_considerations" : 15033.445000066422,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "cribs",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3HCGNV93TJO7R",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "St.Patricks Day",
		"rt_response" : 11158.909999998286,
		"rt_considerations" : 23971.619999967515,
		"age" : 33,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Some college or university",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "h8fwa8b5akuw",
		"consideration1" : "St. Patricks Day",
		"consideration2" : "Christmas",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Neurosurgeon",
		"rt_response" : 25054.18499999996,
		"rt_considerations" : 71197.71500000026,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Pilot",
		"consideration2" : "Taxi Driver",
		"consideration3" : "Neurosurgeon",
		"consideration4" : "Artist",
		"consideration5" : "Athlete",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 11771.23500000016,
		"rt_considerations" : 41448.465000000404,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Stove",
		"consideration2" : "Oven",
		"consideration3" : "Refrigerator",
		"consideration4" : "Toaster",
		"consideration5" : "Dishwasher",
		"consideration6" : "Blender",
		"consideration7" : "Mixer",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "New Years Eve",
		"rt_response" : 13646.990000000194,
		"rt_considerations" : 54055.79500000022,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "Cinco De Mayao",
		"consideration3" : "Independence Day",
		"consideration4" : " Memorial Day",
		"consideration5" : "Labor Day",
		"consideration6" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration7" : "Christmas",
		"consideration8" : "Valentines Day"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Beets",
		"rt_response" : 9521.950000000303,
		"rt_considerations" : 34216.66000000003,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Beets",
		"consideration2" : "Peas",
		"consideration3" : "Carrots",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Underwear",
		"rt_response" : 22623.620000000286,
		"rt_considerations" : 40679.80499999976,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Underwear",
		"consideration2" : "Socks",
		"consideration3" : "Shorts",
		"consideration4" : "Pants",
		"consideration5" : "Shirts",
		"consideration6" : "Jackets",
		"consideration7" : "Coats",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Running",
		"rt_response" : 111822.12499999971,
		"rt_considerations" : 28204.410000000265,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Running",
		"consideration2" : "Swimming",
		"consideration3" : "Baseball",
		"consideration4" : "Football",
		"consideration5" : "Basketball",
		"consideration6" : "Soccer",
		"consideration7" : "Golf",
		"consideration8" : "Tennis"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Burger King",
		"rt_response" : 15115.47499999957,
		"rt_considerations" : 32168.265000000247,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Burger King",
		"consideration2" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration3" : "Wendys",
		"consideration4" : "Arbys",
		"consideration5" : "Dairy Queen",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Bed",
		"rt_response" : 7539.170000000042,
		"rt_considerations" : 32755.675000000396,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Bed",
		"consideration2" : "TV",
		"consideration3" : "Dresser",
		"consideration4" : "Couch",
		"consideration5" : "Night Stand",
		"consideration6" : "Wardrobe",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 6349.430000000168,
		"rt_considerations" : 45960.895000000135,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Elephant",
		"consideration2" : "Zebra",
		"consideration3" : "Lion",
		"consideration4" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration5" : "Chimpanzee",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "ALXW2ZXX4SJRO",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Eggs",
		"rt_response" : 8608.624999999884,
		"rt_considerations" : 21303.315000000177,
		"age" : 53,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "USA",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "h4421boj3dlw",
		"consideration1" : "Eggs",
		"consideration2" : "Bacon",
		"consideration3" : "Toast",
		"consideration4" : "Cereal",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "apple",
		"rt_response" : 3779.5750000077533,
		"rt_considerations" : 13757.945000004838,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "grape",
		"consideration2" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal has the shortest lifespan?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "fly",
		"rt_response" : 4544.294999999693,
		"rt_considerations" : 9776.235000012093,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "moth",
		"consideration2" : "monkey",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "pants",
		"rt_response" : 3241.185000006226,
		"rt_considerations" : 37700.01999998931,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "shirt",
		"consideration2" : "pants",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 4997.795000002952,
		"rt_considerations" : 11489.74000000453,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "bed",
		"consideration2" : "chair",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "dishwasher",
		"rt_response" : 8401.620000004186,
		"rt_considerations" : 8386.520000000019,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "fridge",
		"consideration2" : "stove",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "eggs",
		"rt_response" : 4193.069999993895,
		"rt_considerations" : 10067.399999999907,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "pumpkin",
		"consideration2" : "NA",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job do people stay in for the longest amount of time?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "government",
		"rt_response" : 8699.505000011413,
		"rt_considerations" : 14266.329999998561,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "postal worker",
		"consideration2" : "factory",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport has been around the longest?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "basketball",
		"rt_response" : 4987.419999990379,
		"rt_considerations" : 11519.824999995762,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "football",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most colorful logo?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "macdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 7389.799999989918,
		"rt_considerations" : 8597.259999995003,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "chilis",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AMPMTF5IAAMK8",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "christmas",
		"rt_response" : 4004.6949999959907,
		"rt_considerations" : 11054.109999997308,
		"age" : 39,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "english",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "United States",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "henu8mrq7z0b",
		"consideration1" : "thanksgiving",
		"consideration2" : "christmas",
		"consideration3" : "NA",
		"consideration4" : "NA",
		"consideration5" : "NA",
		"consideration6" : "NA",
		"consideration7" : "NA",
		"consideration8" : "NA"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Blue jeans",
		"rt_response" : 14378.374999971129,
		"rt_considerations" : 71132.14499998139,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Underwear",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable has the most sugar?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "Sweet potatoes",
		"rt_response" : 13203.7400000263,
		"rt_considerations" : 26245.17500004731,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Carrots",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is eaten the most in October?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Eggs",
		"rt_response" : 27891.529999964405,
		"rt_considerations" : 23629.699999990407,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Cereal",
		"consideration2" : "Toast",
		"consideration3" : "Bacon",
		"consideration4" : "Ham",
		"consideration5" : "Oatmeal",
		"consideration6" : "Waffles",
		"consideration7" : "Sausage",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday involves the most drinking?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 35028.02500000689,
		"rt_considerations" : 21781.714999990072,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "New Years Eve",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "St Patricks Day",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Cashier",
		"rt_response" : 6651.389999955427,
		"rt_considerations" : 59675.170000002254,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Sales",
		"consideration2" : "Doctor",
		"consideration3" : "Nurse",
		"consideration4" : "Lawyer",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 6932.675000047311,
		"rt_considerations" : 14421.070000040345,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration2" : "Monkey",
		"consideration3" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Mcdonalds",
		"rt_response" : 7987.734999973327,
		"rt_considerations" : 74299.91499998141,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Taco Bell",
		"consideration2" : "Burger King",
		"consideration3" : "KFC",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "Toaster",
		"rt_response" : 4283.725000044797,
		"rt_considerations" : 60197.449999977835,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Microwave",
		"consideration2" : "Blender",
		"consideration3" : "Coffee maker",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture do people donate the most often?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Couch",
		"rt_response" : 5627.214999985881,
		"rt_considerations" : 37780.079999996815,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Bed",
		"consideration2" : "Table",
		"consideration3" : "Desk",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "AUFOO8PU2BK37",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Basketball",
		"rt_response" : 6187.450000026729,
		"rt_considerations" : 12612.970000016503,
		"age" : 38,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "cvsdpmqm4v6u",
		"consideration1" : "Baseball",
		"consideration2" : "Football",
		"consideration3" : "Hockey",
		"consideration4" : "Soccor",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Ruth Chris",
		"rt_response" : 10542.079999984708,
		"rt_considerations" : 20666.02000000421,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "applebees",
		"consideration2" : "tgi fridays",
		"consideration3" : "ruth chris",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal spends the most time awake?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "monkey",
		"rt_response" : 6064.8199999995995,
		"rt_considerations" : 17969.164999987697,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "elephant",
		"consideration2" : "monkey",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the best eyesight?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "surgeon",
		"rt_response" : 13668.83000000962,
		"rt_considerations" : 22279.494999995222,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "opthamologist",
		"consideration2" : "editor",
		"consideration3" : "surgeon",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food takes the longest to eat?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "pancakes",
		"rt_response" : 8751.749999995809,
		"rt_considerations" : 19770.68999997573,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "eggs",
		"consideration2" : "cereal",
		"consideration3" : "pancakes",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "carrots",
		"rt_response" : 9289.539999997942,
		"rt_considerations" : 20751.464999979362,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "cauliflower",
		"consideration2" : "carrots",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Passover",
		"rt_response" : 7804.574999987381,
		"rt_considerations" : 21007.935000001453,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "Yom Kippur",
		"consideration2" : "Halloween",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance is the noisiest?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 9702.705000003334,
		"rt_considerations" : 18707.45000001625,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "dishwasher",
		"consideration2" : "blender",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most teamwork?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Football",
		"rt_response" : 6994.84499997925,
		"rt_considerations" : 18872.15000001015,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "baseball",
		"consideration2" : "basketball",
		"consideration3" : "football",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would you be most surprised to see in a kitchen?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "couch",
		"rt_response" : 6228.279999981169,
		"rt_considerations" : 16074.705000006361,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "chair",
		"consideration2" : "couch",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A2OROMUVBD1NVC",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item is the most expensive for its weight?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "scarf",
		"rt_response" : 9241.050000011455,
		"rt_considerations" : 16749.580000003334,
		"age" : 56,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Female",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "United States",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "Graduate degree, Masters",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "ghgfd22my5o5",
		"consideration1" : "suit",
		"consideration2" : "shirt",
		"consideration3" : "scarf",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable comes in the most colors?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "pepper",
		"rt_response" : 21232.194999989588,
		"rt_considerations" : 43919.31500000646,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "tomato",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "soccer",
		"rt_response" : 3388.9400000334717,
		"rt_considerations" : 8467.629999970086,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "football",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the worst desserts?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "Apple Bees",
		"rt_response" : 11775.049999996554,
		"rt_considerations" : 7864.470000029542,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "Dennys",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "Waffles",
		"rt_response" : 14926.685000013094,
		"rt_considerations" : 7596.169999975245,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "Pancakes",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the most different names?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Christmas",
		"rt_response" : 4852.42000001017,
		"rt_considerations" : 6011.495000042487,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "Easter",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item comes in the fewest colors?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "Pants",
		"rt_response" : 6355.250000022352,
		"rt_considerations" : 8353.395000041928,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "Gloves",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture would make the best weapon?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "chair",
		"rt_response" : 5056.044999975711,
		"rt_considerations" : 7242.414999986067,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "couch",
		"consideration2" : "table",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance requires the least energy?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "fridge",
		"rt_response" : 3936.2749999854714,
		"rt_considerations" : 7395.124999980908,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "stove",
		"consideration2" : "microwave",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal would you least want to have in your car?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "lion",
		"rt_response" : 6356.2500000116415,
		"rt_considerations" : 8469.975000014529,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "tiger",
		"consideration2" : "leopard",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A3LL096CAY5WHB",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job is the most common one to have?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Retail worker",
		"rt_response" : 6856.280000007246,
		"rt_considerations" : 6111.44000000786,
		"age" : 24,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "High school",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "n1ytf7tnfz6q",
		"consideration1" : "fast food worker",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What zoo animal eats the most for its body weight?",
		"category" : "zoo animals",
		"response" : "Elephant",
		"rt_response" : 32275.98500001477,
		"rt_considerations" : 36715.03500000108,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 1,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "Horse",
		"consideration2" : "Monkey",
		"consideration3" : "Gorilla",
		"consideration4" : "Chimpanzee ",
		"consideration5" : "Penguin",
		"consideration6" : "Giraffe",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What chain restaurant has the most items on their menu?",
		"category" : "chain restaurants",
		"response" : "PF Changs",
		"rt_response" : 10006.095000018831,
		"rt_considerations" : 24795.104999968316,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 2,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "McDonalds",
		"consideration2" : "Applebees",
		"consideration3" : "Burgerking",
		"consideration4" : "Wendys",
		"consideration5" : "Subway",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What piece of furniture can support the least amount of weight?",
		"category" : "types of furniture",
		"response" : "Stool",
		"rt_response" : 7835.62000002712,
		"rt_considerations" : 12713.564999983646,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 3,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "Chair",
		"consideration2" : "Sofa",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What vegetable do people eat most often with breakfast?",
		"category" : "vegetables",
		"response" : "potato",
		"rt_response" : 10715.370000049006,
		"rt_considerations" : 16416.480000014417,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 4,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "na",
		"consideration2" : "na",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What kitchen appliance breaks the most?",
		"category" : "kitchen appliances",
		"response" : "blender",
		"rt_response" : 5380.380000045989,
		"rt_considerations" : 27995.58500002604,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 5,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "toaster",
		"consideration2" : "waffle maker",
		"consideration3" : "mixer",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What job requires the most talking?",
		"category" : "jobs",
		"response" : "Sales",
		"rt_response" : 12613.324999983888,
		"rt_considerations" : 16465.68500000285,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 6,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "receptionist",
		"consideration2" : "manager",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What breakfast food is the most expensive?",
		"category" : "breakfast foods",
		"response" : "bacon",
		"rt_response" : 8485.34000001382,
		"rt_considerations" : 8281.294999993406,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 7,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "sausage",
		"consideration2" : "eggs",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What clothing item do people keep the longest?",
		"category" : "clothing items",
		"response" : "coat",
		"rt_response" : 5179.5900000142865,
		"rt_considerations" : 11551.929999957792,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 8,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "sweater",
		"consideration2" : "tennis shoes",
		"consideration3" : "na",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What holiday has the worst food associated with it?",
		"category" : "holidays",
		"response" : "Easter",
		"rt_response" : 39599.65499996906,
		"rt_considerations" : 13514.28499998292,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 9,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "Christmas",
		"consideration2" : "Thanksgiving",
		"consideration3" : "4th of July",
		"consideration4" : "na",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	},
	{
		"subject_id" : "A23VWLX98JNB0Z",
		"exp_type" : "response",
		"question" : "What sport requires the most agility?",
		"category" : "sports",
		"response" : "Runner",
		"rt_response" : 9478.050000034273,
		"rt_considerations" : 18499.354999978095,
		"age" : 25,
		"student" : "No",
		"gender" : "Male",
		"language" : "English",
		"country" : "USA",
		"nationality" : "American",
		"education" : "College or university degree",
		"trial_order" : 10,
		"turk_code" : "bccpa320y2xs",
		"consideration1" : "Football",
		"consideration2" : "Soccer",
		"consideration3" : "Baseball",
		"consideration4" : "Basketball",
		"consideration5" : "na",
		"consideration6" : "na",
		"consideration7" : "na",
		"consideration8" : "na"
	}
]
